<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pulse</title><link>/</link><description>Recent posts from on Pulse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Happy New Year, everyone! Welcome to 2026.</title><link>/post/happy-2026/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/happy-2026/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Happy New Year, everyone! Welcome to 2026.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the calendar turns a new page, I find myself reflecting on the moments that brought us here—the joys, the challenges, and the quiet resilience we’ve all built. As per my yearly tradition, I wanted to share something that grounds me and brings peace to my soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No matter what this new year holds, there is timeless comfort to be found in the words of the Quran. Here are 10 verses that I hope will wrap your heart in warmth, remind you of your strength, and reassure you that you are never walking alone. May 2026 be a year of ease, growth, and abundant mercy for us all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For when the path feels uncertain
&amp;ldquo;And He is with you wherever you are.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Surah Al-Hadid (57:4)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="2"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A promise of relief
&amp;ldquo;For indeed, with hardship [will be] ease. Indeed, with hardship [will be] ease.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Surah Ash-Sharh (94:5-6)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="3"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For the moments you feel unheard
&amp;ldquo;When My servants ask you concerning Me, indeed I am near. I respond to the invocation of the supplicant when he calls upon Me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Surah Al-Baqarah (2:186)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="4"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you need a fresh start
&amp;ldquo;Say, &amp;lsquo;O My servants who have transgressed against themselves [by sinning], do not despair of the mercy of Allah. Indeed, Allah forgives all sins. Indeed, it is He who is the Forgiving, the Merciful.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Surah Az-Zumar (39:53)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="5"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A reminder of your strength
&amp;ldquo;Allah does not burden a soul beyond that it can bear.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Surah Al-Baqarah (2:286)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="6"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For ultimate tranquility
&amp;ldquo;Those who have believed and whose hearts are assured by the remembrance of Allah. Unquestionably, by the remembrance of Allah hearts are assured.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Surah Ar-Ra&amp;rsquo;d (13:28)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="7"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you need hope for the future
&amp;ldquo;You know not; perhaps Allah will bring about, after that, a [new] matter.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Surah At-Talaq (65:1)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="8"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A reminder of His immense love
&amp;ldquo;My mercy encompasses all things.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Surah Al-A&amp;rsquo;raf (7:156)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="9"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For never feeling abandoned
&amp;ldquo;Your Lord has not taken leave of you, [O Muhammad], nor has He detested [you].&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Surah Ad-Duha (93:3)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="10"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The secret to abundance in 2026
&amp;ldquo;If you are grateful, I will surely increase you [in favor].&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Surah Ibrahim (14:7)&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Stereo Amplifiers: The Audiophile's choice for 2.1 and Vinyl</title><link>/post/amp-versus-reciever/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/amp-versus-reciever/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;For listeners whose primary focus is two-channel (stereo) music listening, especially the rich, analog sound of vinyl records, a dedicated integrated stereo amplifier (often just called a stereo amplifier) is generally preferred over a multi-channel AV receiver (AVR). This preference is rooted in audio fidelity, design philosophy, and specific requirements for turntable playback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus on Audio Purity and Quality
An integrated stereo amplifier is designed with a single, uncompromising goal: to take a two-channel signal and amplify it with the highest possible fidelity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dedicated Resources: A stereo amplifier channels its entire budget and design effort into only two amplifier channels (Left and Right), plus a pre-amplifier section. This means the manufacturer can invest in higher-quality components for the power supply, capacitors, and internal circuitry compared to an AVR at a similar price point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Less Interference (Simpler Design): AV receivers are complex hubs that house not only multiple amplifier channels (5.1, 7.1, 9.2, etc.) but also numerous video processors, digital-to-analog converters (DACs), and surround-sound decoding chips (Dolby Atmos, DTS:X, etc.). This abundance of digital and video circuitry in close proximity can introduce electrical noise that can subtly degrade the delicate analog audio signal. A stereo amplifier has a much simpler internal layout, leading to a &amp;ldquo;cleaner&amp;rdquo; signal path.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Targeted Power: While an AVR may advertise high wattage, that power is often split among seven or more channels. A dedicated stereo amplifier&amp;rsquo;s power rating is solely for the two main channels, ensuring it can better drive demanding or larger stereo speakers to their full potential without strain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="2"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Essential Phono Stage for Turntables
The signal produced by a turntable&amp;rsquo;s cartridge is extremely weak and requires special treatment—it is not a standard &amp;ldquo;line-level&amp;rdquo; signal like that from a CD player or streamer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amplification and Equalization: A turntable signal needs to be amplified to line level, and it also requires RIAA equalization (Recording Industry Association of America curve) to correct the severe low-frequency cut and high-frequency boost applied during the vinyl mastering process. This essential component is called a phono stage or phono preamp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Superior Built-in Phono Stages: High-quality integrated stereo amplifiers, particularly those built by hi-fi companies, are much more likely to include a high-performance, dedicated phono input. This built-in phono stage is often superior in quality to the one found in budget-to-mid-range AV receivers, which may treat the phono stage as an afterthought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Analog Preservation: Vinyl playback is a fundamentally analog process. Stereo amplifiers are typically better optimized for handling, preserving, and amplifying this purely analog signal path without unnecessary digital conversion, which can be critical for audiophiles seeking the authentic &amp;ldquo;warmth&amp;rdquo; of vinyl.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Firecrawl LLM Ready AWS Bedrock RAG</title><link>/post/fire-crawl/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/fire-crawl/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey AI builders! Tired of dealing with messy HTML when trying to ground your AWS Bedrock applications with real-world data?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet Firecrawl (&lt;a href="https://www.firecrawl.dev"&gt;https://www.firecrawl.dev&lt;/a&gt;), the AI-first web crawling and scraping API that&amp;rsquo;s changing the RAG game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is Firecrawl?
Firecrawl is designed to solve the headache of getting clean web data for Large Language Models (LLMs). Instead of wrestling with traditional scrapers, Firecrawl:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crawls entire websites or scrapes single pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cleans the content automatically (removes headers, footers, ads).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Converts it into clean, LLM-optimized formats like Markdown or structured JSON.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It handles JavaScript rendering and anti-bot measures, so your focus stays on building, not fixing broken scrapers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bedrock Connection 💡
For anyone building applications on AWS Bedrock—especially those using Knowledge Bases and Agents for Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG)—Firecrawl is a perfect complementary tool:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;High-Quality Knowledge Bases: Bedrock Knowledge Bases are essential for grounding FMs like Claude and Llama. Firecrawl ensures the data you ingest is already clean, perfectly formatted (Markdown is excellent for RAG), and highly relevant, leading to better retrieval accuracy and fewer hallucinations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Agent Tools: You can integrate the Firecrawl API directly into your Bedrock Agents as a custom tool, allowing your agent to perform real-time, intelligent scraping and data extraction when needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re using Bedrock, check out Firecrawl to streamline your data pipeline and start feeding your models the high-quality, structured data they deserve!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Architecting Tomorrow</title><link>/post/introducing-its-architeture-group/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/introducing-its-architeture-group/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Explore the future of IT at UCSB with &amp;ldquo;Architecting Tomorrow,&amp;rdquo; a short film introducing our Enterprise Architecture group! This video provides an engaging, animated look into who we are, what we do, and our vision for a more connected and efficient technological landscape at UCSB.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this video, you&amp;rsquo;ll meet the expert team dedicated to bridging the gap between vision and implementation in IT. We&amp;rsquo;ll cover:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why It Matters: Discover why architecture is crucial in IT, helping to manage complexity, ensure sustainability, and bring clarity and alignment to technology solutions at UCSB. We embrace best practices, stay cutting-edge, ensure consistency, and plan for the future, acting as guides rather than enforcers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s Next: See how we aim to be a valuable resource for you through consultation, guidance, review, and collaboration. We are also looking to define how our group best fits future needs, elevate common pain points, and develop a pattern for Cloud Native Application Development to accelerate innovation and improve reliability. Our plans also include standardizing and strengthening the data foundation, advancing analytical reporting capabilities, and enabling scalable, intelligent data use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This presentation highlights our collective expertise in AWS Certified Solutions Architecture, large-scale software system design, data analytics, big data, machine learning, and artificial intelligence, coupled with an in-depth understanding of Campus business processes and domains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We guide, not gatekeep, bridging vision to execution—together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;"&gt;
&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TaeADzCrFjw?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description></item><item><title>Bedrock's Game Changer: Why Cross-Region LLM Inference is a Must-Have</title><link>/post/bedrock/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/bedrock/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;As Chief Software Architect at UC Santa Barbara, I focus on integrating cutting-edge cloud features like AWS Bedrock. For enterprise LLM deployment, we must solve three non-negotiables: latency, data gravity, and resiliency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cross-region inference in Bedrock is the definitive answer, moving LLM strategy from experiment to production-grade architecture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Pillars of Multi-Region LLM Architecture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;High Resiliency and Failover
Single-region deployment is a critical vulnerability. Cross-region inference allows immediate, automatic failover (e.g., from us-east-1 to us-west-2). This maintains API parity and model consistency across geographies, guaranteeing uninterrupted service for critical applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data Gravity and Compliance
International operation mandates that data processing often occurs where the data resides (Data Gravity). This is essential for compliance (e.g., GDPR). Cross-region inference lets us run the same foundational model locally (e.g., in eu-central-1), keeping prompts and responses within necessary jurisdictional boundaries while standardizing the service platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Global Latency Optimization
For interactive applications, every millisecond counts. By intelligently routing user requests to the closest available and operational endpoint, cross-region deployment minimizes network latency. This ensures a fast, consistent, and performant user experience for a global user base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Architect’s Mandate&lt;/strong&gt;
Bedrock handles the model deployment complexity. Our focus shifts to the infrastructure:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart Routing:&lt;/strong&gt; Using services like Route 53 for latency-based routing to the fastest region.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global State:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensuring conversational state (chat history) is managed in a globally replicated, low-latency data store (like DynamoDB Global Tables).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cross-region inference is the essential capability for building the next generation of resilient, compliant, and globally distributed LLM applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts on state management in this multi-region environment? Let&amp;rsquo;s connect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="text-align: center;"&gt;
&lt;img src="../../img/bedrock.png" alt="AWS Bedrock" width="600" height="600" style="width: 400px; height: 400px; border: 5px solid blue; margin: 0 auto; display: block;"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#AWS #Bedrock #LLM #SoftwareArchitecture #CloudComputing #UCSB&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Review of David Gilmour's new album : Luck and Strange</title><link>/post/review-luckandstrange/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/review-luckandstrange/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 David Gilmour’s much-anticipated album Luck and Strange dropped on September 6, marking his first release in nine years since Rattle That Lock. Fans were eagerly waiting, especially after preview tracks like &amp;ldquo;The Piper’s Call,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Between Two Points,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Dark and Velvet Nights&amp;rdquo; hinted at a mix of the familiar Pink Floyd essence and something new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gilmour doesn’t disappoint. Luck and Strange is a beautifully crafted work with his signature sound—soaring guitar solos, bluesy undertones, and moments of poignant calm. The album features contributions from his family: daughter Romany shines on &amp;ldquo;Between Two Points&amp;rdquo; and duets on the bonus track &amp;ldquo;Yes, I Have Ghosts.&amp;rdquo; His late Pink Floyd bandmate Rick Wright&amp;rsquo;s electric piano, recorded years before, also makes an appearance, further deepening the connection to his past.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Standout tracks include &amp;ldquo;Black Cat,&amp;rdquo; an instrumental opener that gently pulls you into the album’s mood, and the title track &amp;ldquo;Luck and Strange,&amp;rdquo; where Wright’s piano and Gilmour’s guitar interplay soar. Meanwhile, tracks like &amp;ldquo;Dark and Velvet Nights&amp;rdquo; offer a more rugged, earthy vibe, contrasting beautifully with the softer, acoustic-driven moments like &amp;ldquo;A Single Spark.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite some experimentation—partly due to the influence of producer Charlie Andrew, who pushed Gilmour to explore new directions—it remains unmistakably a Gilmour record. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s his delicate balance of styles or his signature guitar mastery, Luck and Strange offers a compelling listen. While Gilmour himself suggested it might be his best work since The Dark Side of the Moon, that remains to be seen, as the album still needs time to grow on listeners. For now, it stands as a strong contender, even if it hasn&amp;rsquo;t reached the heights of classics like Wish You Were Here just yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In short, Luck and Strange is a must-listen for any Gilmour or Pink Floyd fan, offering plenty of depth and maturity with every play. It’s an album that’s sure to grow on you, proving that Gilmour’s magic is still very much alive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;"&gt;
&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wBdW8fHPy-8?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description></item><item><title>Some updates of me</title><link>/post/updates/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/updates/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone! I know it&amp;rsquo;s been a while since my last update – things have been incredibly busy with both work and my YouTube channel!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work Update:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the professional side, we’re making solid progress on our massive ERP project: the Oracle Financial Cloud deployment. This project is a beast, with over a hundred swim lanes of technical and functional scopes. It’s definitely a challenge to keep up with everything that needs to be done between now and our launch date in July 2025. But hey, nothing worth doing ever comes easy, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personal News:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a personal note, my &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/@igluonvinyls"&gt;YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt; is growing faster than I ever imagined! I’ve almost hit 200 posts and, as of now, I have 609 subscribers! 🎉 I never thought I’d see this level of engagement, so I’m feeling incredibly grateful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lately, I’ve been experimenting with a podcast-style album/music review format. My first one, on David Gilmour’s new &amp;lsquo;&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/wBdW8fHPy-8?si=I5l8ap8v8BrQQWmo"&gt;Luck and Strange&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo; album, was a hit! The positive feedback has motivated me, so stay tuned for another review coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tech Front:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve also been diving deeper into cinematography, color grading, and video editing to make my content even more immersive. It’s a learning curve, but I&amp;rsquo;m loving every moment of it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you’re all doing well. If you get a chance, swing by my &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/@igluonvinyls"&gt;YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt; – would love to hear your thoughts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take care and God bless!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>My YouTube Channel iGluon</title><link>/post/igluon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/igluon/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Those who know or follow me know I had my own Sole proprietorship in the early 1990s. I am very proud of what I did with my business back then; unfortunately, I had to close that business eventually due to demand from my daytime job. Recently, I started a new YouTube channel based on my old business name, &amp;ldquo;iGluon.&amp;rdquo; I have a lot of ideas to create content that users may find helpful. But for now, I posted a few videos; the acceptance was incredible. In less than a month, my channel got over 8,000 views. My subscriber grew from 3 to 28 also. This is good progress, and I would love to keep up the momentum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is my YouTube Channel, please visit, like if you enjoy my videos and suggest future content. Look forward to seeing you all in my YouTube channel! &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/@igluonvinyls"&gt;iGluon Vinyls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Embracing 2024: A Year of Reflection and Renewal</title><link>/post/welcome-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/welcome-2024/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we step into the fresh canvas of 2024, I find myself in a reflective mood, contemplating the journey we&amp;rsquo;ve all been through and the exciting path that lies ahead. This isn&amp;rsquo;t just another year; it&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity for growth, resilience, and embracing new possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the realm of software development, the pace of innovation continues to astonish us. As the Chief Software Architect at the University of California, Santa Barbara, I&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed firsthand the remarkable strides we&amp;rsquo;ve made in technology. The challenges we face are met with ingenious solutions, and our commitment to pushing boundaries remains unwavering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the personal front, being a father to a wonderful daughter and celebrating almost 27 years of marriage with my wife brings a profound sense of joy and gratitude. Family has been my anchor, providing support and love that fuels my professional endeavors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward, my aspirations for 2024 extend beyond the realm of code and algorithms. It&amp;rsquo;s about fostering connections, nurturing relationships, and making a positive impact on the world around us. Each day is an opportunity to learn, grow, and contribute to something greater than ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we embark on this new chapter, let&amp;rsquo;s embrace the challenges and triumphs that come our way. May 2024 be a year of innovation, kindness, and personal and professional accomplishments. Here&amp;rsquo;s to the journey ahead, filled with exciting possibilities and the unwavering spirit to make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wishing you all a fantastic New Year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers,
Yaheya Quazi&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Exciting Milestone in my Software Engineering Journey!</title><link>/post/pc-to-mac/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/pc-to-mac/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share a monumental shift in my 30-plus years of software engineering career – the decision to make the Mac my primary work station! 🍎&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking back, my journey began with Windows, possibly starting with the era of Windows 3.0. It&amp;rsquo;s where I acquired my foundational computing skills and built the pillars of my engineering career, primarily on various Microsoft platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As technology advanced, so did my tools. Today, nearly everything essential for my work seamlessly runs on a Mac. From &lt;em&gt;Visual Studio Code/Visual Studio&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Microsoft Office&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Edge/Chrome Browser&lt;/em&gt;, to &lt;em&gt;Azure Data Studio&lt;/em&gt; (a shift from SSMS), and &lt;em&gt;.Net Core&lt;/em&gt; – each performs as well, if not better, than on my trusted Windows platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="current-workstation-mac-mini"&gt;Current Workstation: Mac Mini&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apple M2 Pro Chip:&lt;/strong&gt; The powerhouse behind my Mac Mini, providing efficient processing and performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;16 GB Memory:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensuring smooth multitasking capabilities, crucial for handling complex software development tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;512 GB SSD HD:&lt;/strong&gt; Ample storage space for my projects and applications, contributing to faster data access and overall system responsiveness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sonoma 14.2.1:&lt;/strong&gt; Running on the latest Sonoma version, embracing the latest features and enhancements in the Mac ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="previous-machine-dell-inspiron"&gt;Previous Machine: Dell Inspiron&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Farewell to my faithful Dell Inspiron, a workhorse that served me well:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intel i7 Processor:&lt;/strong&gt; Delivering the processing power needed for demanding development tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;32 GB RAM:&lt;/strong&gt; Enabling seamless multitasking and efficient handling of resource-intensive applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;265 GB SSD HD:&lt;/strong&gt; While slightly smaller than my Mac&amp;rsquo;s storage, it provided sufficient space for my projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Windows 11:&lt;/strong&gt; The operating system that accompanied me through numerous coding marathons and project completions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This transition signifies more than just a change in hardware and operating systems. It&amp;rsquo;s a shift in perspective, embracing new possibilities and exploring the full potential of the Mac ecosystem as my primary development environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s to embracing change, continuous learning, and the exciting journey ahead in the realm of software engineering! 🚀💻 #MacSwitch #SoftwareEngineeringJourney #NewBeginnings&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Depeche Mode Suffer Well Vinyl</title><link>/post/depeche-mode-suffer-well/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/depeche-mode-suffer-well/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Diving into the final chapter of our Depeche Mode series with &amp;ldquo;Suffer Well.&amp;rdquo; 🎶 Immerse yourself in the magnetic sounds of Dave Gahan that truly captivate in this track. 🌟 Enjoy the ride! 🚀 Also, spiced it up with clips from the unforgettable Memento Mori concert in Las Vegas, December 2023. 🎤🔥&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;"&gt;
&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/h5PvEOtPeEo?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description></item><item><title>Phil Collins &amp; Philip Bailey Vinyl</title><link>/post/phil-collins-easy-lover/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/phil-collins-easy-lover/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 Immerse yourself in the timeless melodies of Phil Collins! 📀 Our latest video features his iconic music, creating a nostalgic vinyl experience. 🚫 No copyright infringement is intended; we&amp;rsquo;re sharing the magic of music purely for the love of it. 💙 Support the artist by grabbing the record and let the tunes become a cherished part of your collection! 🎶 #PhilCollins #VinylExperience #MusicLovers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;"&gt;
&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uUNBreqB3FA?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description></item><item><title>Depeche Mode Concert Memento Mori</title><link>/post/depeche-mode-concert/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/depeche-mode-concert/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Attended Depeche Mode Concert Memento Mori at Las Vegas on 12/1/2023. My Youtube Post shows some of it, hope you enjoy -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;"&gt;
&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/R1_x_jVgk4E?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description></item><item><title>Classic Hits in Vinyl Record</title><link>/post/pl-beegees/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/pl-beegees/</guid><description>
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;"&gt;
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/videoseries?list=PLxWZIul5j9h5FWn7FZ_Urv5IIzPn4e6OZ" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description></item><item><title>iGluon Youtube Channel Playlists</title><link>/post/youtubeplaylist/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/youtubeplaylist/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Following playlists are now available in my Youtube Channel iGluon. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="../pl-beegees"&gt;Classic Hits in Vinyl Record&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>In the air tonight - Phil Collins</title><link>/post/in-the-air-tonight/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/in-the-air-tonight/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This post is a duplicate of the previous one due to a software glitch that caused sound issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🎶 Take a trip down memory lane with the timeless classic &amp;ldquo;In the Air Tonight&amp;rdquo; by Phil Collins, played on a vintage vinyl record. Let the warm crackle and rich tones transport you back in time. 🕰️ Sit back, relax, and experience the magic of this iconic track as it spins on the turntable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Music © Phil Collins. No copyright infringement is intended. The video contains copyrighted music, which we use to share the vinyl experience. We do not want to profit from its use, nor will we. Instead, we encourage viewers to purchase the record themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;"&gt;
&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eN_uq3AV8Ro?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays and New year 2023</title><link>/post/quran/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/quran/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The year 2023 is approaching us quickly. At the end of 2022, I would like to share 12 hand-picked ayaat (verses) from the Quran. May 2023 brings you happiness, peace and prosper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So remember me I will remember you: Baqarah 152&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Indeed, the mercy of Allah is near to the doers of good. Alaraf 56&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every soul will taste death. And We test you with evil and with good as trial; and to Us you will be returned. Anbiya 35&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is not the eyes that are blind but the hearts Al-Haj 46&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repel evil with that which is better. Al Muminun 96&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perhaps it is close behind you - some of that for which you are impatient. Namlayat 72&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be, and it is. His command is only when he inteds a thing that he says to it &amp;ldquo;Be, and it is&amp;rdquo; Yasin 82&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is the reward for good [anything] but good? Ar-Rahman 60&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And whoever puts all his trust in Allah (SWT) he will be enough for him At-Talaq 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Verily with every hardship comes ease Ash-Sharh 5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And when I am ill, it is He who cures me Ash-Shuara 80&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recite in the name of your Lord who created man from a clinging substance. Al-Alaq 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</description></item><item><title>Various Trading Tools/Techniques</title><link>/post/trade-technique/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/trade-technique/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This post is to introduce to you various Trading Tools and Techniques that may be helpful to you. So let&amp;rsquo;s get on with the list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VIX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</description></item><item><title>YouTube Handle</title><link>/post/youtube-handles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/youtube-handles/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This post will be a short post for those have a YouTube channel. Google recently introduced, Youtube Handles. YouTube handles helps make it easier for members of the community to find and connect with each other. Your handle will be unique to your channel and will be how people mention you in comments, community posts, and more. My YouTube channel handle is iGluonVinyls. Once you have your unique handle name, then you can get a unique URL for your channel as well. For example mine is &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/igluonvinyls"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/igluonvinyls&lt;/a&gt; This URL is much easier to remember than the previous GUID based URL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn more about YouTube handles you can go &lt;a href="https://www.business-standard.com/article/technology/youtube-introduces-handle-feature-know-what-is-it-how-it-works-and-more-122102800179_1.html#:~:text=As%20the%20handles%20are%20unique,they%20are%20not%20on%20YouTube."&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My YouTube channel is here -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/@igluonvinyls"&gt;iGluon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Pink Floyd Concert in Los Angeles - Roger with brothers!</title><link>/post/pinkfloyd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/pinkfloyd/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I am a classic Rock fan. I bought a ticket to go with my brothers and daughter to see Roger Waters - This is not a drill in Cryptoarena Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The quality of the concert, sound, the environment was absolutely unreal to say the least. However, I must admit Roger&amp;rsquo;s politics is truly crazy. A picture collage of the event with family is below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="../../img/roger-with-brothers.jpg" alt="Roger with Brothers" title="Top Level Demonstration of Pulse Site" width="400" height="350" align="center" /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I post a video of the opening in YouTube which got an expected number of views in a short time. Feel free to watch it &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/OUgTpLPYNrE"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 08-22-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-08222022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-08222022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A disastrous day and has been for almost a week now for all indices. S&amp;amp;P dropped a solid 2.14 percent. Vis spiked up 15.53 percent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cash out for next moderate/severe inflation (2023 most likely)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/08/21/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html"&gt;Dow slumps more than 600 points as summer rally fades&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/18/china-holdings-of-us-debt-fall-below-1-trillion-for-the-first-time-since-2010.html"&gt;China holdings of U.S. debt fall below $1 trillion for the first time since 2010&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/18/netflix-investors-brace-for-subscriber-losses-as-company-builds-for-long-term.html"&gt;Netflix investors brace for subscriber losses as company works on long-term fixes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tipranks.com/news/blurbs/new-buy-rating-for-tesla-tsla-the-consumer-goods-giant-3"&gt;New Buy Rating for Tesla (TSLA), the Consumer Goods Giant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tesmanian.com/blogs/tesmanian-blog/analysts-confident-in-teslas-strong-growth-outlook-despite-q2-2022-slowdown"&gt;Analysts Confident in Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Strong Growth Outlook Despite Q2 Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 08-17-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-08172022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-08172022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;33,980.32&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-180.25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.69&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4,274.04&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-32.31&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.84&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12,938.12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-92.37&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.81&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,987.31&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-5.96&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.34&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;19.90&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.07&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After almost a month break, I am back writing my closing bells post. Work and personal commitments kept me writing these posts regularly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot has changed in the market in the last four weeks. It is with great pleasure we see some upside to the market, although today seem to be a wide spread down day on all three major indices. &lt;a href="../glosarry"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; is larking around 20-21 range. Remember, just a month or so back, it was around 30!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite all these positive news, major analysts predict that a mild to a severe recession is facing us perhaps early to mid 2023. One can argue, we are already in a recession as GDP growth has been negative for two consecutive quarters. &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/cea/written-materials/2022/07/21/how-do-economists-determine-whether-the-economy-is-in-a-recession/"&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is a great article on how economists determine, if we are on a recession.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biden administration passed an impressive &amp;ldquo;Inflation Reduction Act&amp;rdquo; that may aid the market. Although, some experts argue, the additional government spending (almost a trillion dollars) may put gasoline on inflation fire that is burning out of control. Speaking on inflation, we continue to observe a slight downward trend in July which was accepted widely by the market. Gas prices has been consistently going down which is also a positive sign that we may end a soft landing and avoid a recession.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Retail investors need to be cautious now than ever in my opinion. This is a difficult time, and the 2020, invest and get 100 % return on most stocks are gone. Now we see traditional 10-15 % return, if we are lucky. Most portfolios have been slashed 40-50 % depending on how aggressive your investment strategy is. Despite, all this caution, US economy is one that is strong. Most do not win betting against this giant. In my opinion, the US market will again see a bull trend, however, there maybe pain before we get there for sure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cash out for next moderate/severe inflation (2023 most likely)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/18/ibm-earnings-q2-2022.html"&gt;IBM shares slide after company trims cash forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/18/china-holdings-of-us-debt-fall-below-1-trillion-for-the-first-time-since-2010.html"&gt;China holdings of U.S. debt fall below $1 trillion for the first time since 2010&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/18/netflix-investors-brace-for-subscriber-losses-as-company-builds-for-long-term.html"&gt;Netflix investors brace for subscriber losses as company works on long-term fixes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tipranks.com/news/blurbs/new-buy-rating-for-tesla-tsla-the-consumer-goods-giant-3"&gt;New Buy Rating for Tesla (TSLA), the Consumer Goods Giant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tesmanian.com/blogs/tesmanian-blog/analysts-confident-in-teslas-strong-growth-outlook-despite-q2-2022-slowdown"&gt;Analysts Confident in Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Strong Growth Outlook Despite Q2 Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>My reflections on Suratul Taha</title><link>/post/taha/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/taha/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This post is different than what I have usually post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sura is Taha in Quran, and the sura summarizes the entire adventure when Allah appeared to Prophet Musa in the holy mountains of Tuwa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a few consecutive Ayaat, the sura describes the conversation between Allah and Musa. One of these conversations that touches me the most is when Allah asked Musa to go to Feraun to spread his word. Musa asks Allah, among other wishes, to remove his stutter and give him strength so that his voice and appearance are convincible to Feraun. Allah accepts his desire and says, &amp;ldquo;All that you requested has been granted, O Moses! &amp;quot; instantaneously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine for a second the magnitude of this event. You are standing in front of all merciful and generous Allah, having a dialogue with him, asking for your needs, and instantly they are granted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While we probably will not meet Allah in this world, we may not get the granted assurance from Allah instantly either. Nevertheless, Allah says, &amp;ldquo;So remember me, I will remember you.&amp;rdquo; The Ayaat essentially means the same wish-granting promise as Musa, except perhaps we are not hearing or feeling the presence of Allah just in front of us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our duas are one of the highest Ibadah we can perform and one that Allah prefers. We should never go astray from it and have faith that they are all being heard, and in time we will get the appropriate response that is best for us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are all struggling in our lives one way or the other. I hope this post encourages you that you are not alone and that Allah is waiting to hear from you; you have to call him!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the quotation from Quran, the specific ayah discussed in post -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:24 Go to Pharaoh, for he has truly transgressed all bounds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:25 Moses prayed, &amp;ldquo;My Lord! Uplift my heart for me,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:26 and make my task easy,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:27 and remove the impediment from my tongue&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:28 so people may understand my speech,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:29 and grant me a helper from my family,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:30 Aaron, my brother.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:31 Strengthen me through him,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:32 and let him share my task,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:33 so that we may glorify You much&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:34 and remember You much,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:35 for truly You have ˹always˺ been overseeing us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20:36 Allah responded, &amp;ldquo;All that you requested has been granted, O Moses!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And here is Raad Mohammad reciting sura Taha like no other -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JWt5_NJuhME&amp;amp;t=636s"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JWt5_NJuhME&amp;amp;t=636s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 07-18-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-07182022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-07182022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;31,072.61&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-215.65&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.69&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,830.85&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-32.31&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.84&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,360.05&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-92.37&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.81&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,738.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-5.96&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.34&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25.30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.07&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What a turn of events. Dow up 350 plus in the early trading, only to close -216 at the closing. All major indices gave up their gains and went into solid red. VIX edged up almost 5 percent. At the time of writing this post, all indices futures are flat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earning season is upon us. Netflix investors brace for subscriber losses as company works on long-term fixes. Tesla gets a new Buy rating, and the stock rallied in the early morning. Unfortunately, gave up all the gains by the end of day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for signs of market bottoming, which may have already happened.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch for inflation flatten up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/18/ibm-earnings-q2-2022.html"&gt;IBM shares slide after company trims cash forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/18/china-holdings-of-us-debt-fall-below-1-trillion-for-the-first-time-since-2010.html"&gt;China holdings of U.S. debt fall below $1 trillion for the first time since 2010&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/18/netflix-investors-brace-for-subscriber-losses-as-company-builds-for-long-term.html"&gt;Netflix investors brace for subscriber losses as company works on long-term fixes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tipranks.com/news/blurbs/new-buy-rating-for-tesla-tsla-the-consumer-goods-giant-3"&gt;New Buy Rating for Tesla (TSLA), the Consumer Goods Giant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tesmanian.com/blogs/tesmanian-blog/analysts-confident-in-teslas-strong-growth-outlook-despite-q2-2022-slowdown"&gt;Analysts Confident in Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Strong Growth Outlook Despite Q2 Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 07-15-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-07152022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-07152022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;31,288.26&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-192.51&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.62&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,863.16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;72.78&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.92&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,452.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;201.24&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.79&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,744.37&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;36.87&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;24.23&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-2.17&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-8.22&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have taken few days break from writing my closing bell summary. Many things have happened in the last few days, unfortunately market taking a turn for the worst. All indices were mostly negative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, there is much needed market rally with all indices in solid green territory and also VIX dropping below 25.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a to a Market Bull run in 3/4 quarter of 2022!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for signs of market bottoming, which may have already happened.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch for inflation flatten up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/06/asia-markets.html?&amp;amp;qsearchterm=china%20covid"&gt;Greater China stocks fall as Covid concerns resurge; Asia-Pacific markets fall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.morningstar.com/articles/1101564/markets-brief-ahead-of-the-next-cpi-report-more-signs-inflation-is-peaking"&gt;Markets Brief: Ahead of the Next CPI Report, More Signs Inflation is Peaking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/05/oil-tumbles-more-than-8percent-breaks-below-100-as-recession-fears-mount.html"&gt;Oil tumbles as much as 10%, breaks below $100 as recession fears mount&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://electrek.co/2022/07/06/tesla-worlds-largest-electric-car-producer/"&gt;Tesla is still the world’s largest electric car producer despite what you are hearing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tesmanian.com/blogs/tesmanian-blog/analysts-confident-in-teslas-strong-growth-outlook-despite-q2-2022-slowdown"&gt;Analysts Confident in Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Strong Growth Outlook Despite Q2 Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 07-12-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-07122022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-07122022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30,981.33&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-192.51&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.62&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,818.80&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-35.63&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.92&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,364.73&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-107.87&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.95&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,728.18&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-3.83&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.22&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;27.29&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4.28&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet another red day - VERY red day I should add. All eyes are on tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s CPI report. I think market is pricing in a very bad news. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe Powell fooled us stating &amp;ldquo;Inflation is transitory&amp;rdquo;. What happened to the &amp;ldquo;transition&amp;rdquo;? It feels like the inflation is here to stay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TSLA had a brutal day, although at the near closing of market it recovered most of the loss which is good. Day traders are in this market like a hawk. They are making money on the massive volatility. Can&amp;rsquo;t say I can blame them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NIO recovered a tiny bit from last couple of days sell off. Chinese Covid fear causing massive FUD. VIX is up almost 10 percent in the last two days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crypto appears to be stuck on Crypto winter. I have read the bottom should be in Q3 of 2022 with Q4 a bull run. Prediction S&amp;amp;P ends the year between 4700-4900.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for signs of market bottoming, which may have already happened.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch for inflation flatten up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/06/asia-markets.html?&amp;amp;qsearchterm=china%20covid"&gt;Greater China stocks fall as Covid concerns resurge; Asia-Pacific markets fall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.morningstar.com/articles/1101564/markets-brief-ahead-of-the-next-cpi-report-more-signs-inflation-is-peaking"&gt;Markets Brief: Ahead of the Next CPI Report, More Signs Inflation is Peaking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/05/oil-tumbles-more-than-8percent-breaks-below-100-as-recession-fears-mount.html"&gt;Oil tumbles as much as 10%, breaks below $100 as recession fears mount&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://electrek.co/2022/07/06/tesla-worlds-largest-electric-car-producer/"&gt;Tesla is still the world’s largest electric car producer despite what you are hearing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tesmanian.com/blogs/tesmanian-blog/analysts-confident-in-teslas-strong-growth-outlook-despite-q2-2022-slowdown"&gt;Analysts Confident in Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Strong Growth Outlook Despite Q2 Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 07-11-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-07112022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-07112022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;31,173.84&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-164.31&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.52&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,854.43&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-44.95&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-1.15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,372.60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-262.71&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-2.26&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,732.01&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-37.36&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-2.11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;26.17&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.53&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;6.21&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Massive red day - S&amp;amp;P given up almost all the gains from the week prior. It appears, the market takes one step forward two step backward; I don&amp;rsquo;t see how it may change any time soon. &lt;a href="../glosarry"&gt;Vix&lt;/a&gt; went up more than 6 percent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chinese stocks took a beating as Covid concern raises yet again. Shanghai will be conducting mass testing in several districts after Covid cases were detected earlier this week, a statement on the city’s WeChat account said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the time of writing this post, Tesla, NIO both took beating down 6.55 and 9.06 respectively. NIO down from its recent highs almost 12 percent. Tesla gave up all the after market gain Friday and some more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All eyes are on Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;CPI&lt;/a&gt; numbers. There are more signs inflation is peaking with no sign of it being under control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for signs of market bottoming, which may have already happened.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch for inflation flatten up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/06/asia-markets.html?&amp;amp;qsearchterm=china%20covid"&gt;Greater China stocks fall as Covid concerns resurge; Asia-Pacific markets fall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.morningstar.com/articles/1101564/markets-brief-ahead-of-the-next-cpi-report-more-signs-inflation-is-peaking"&gt;Markets Brief: Ahead of the Next CPI Report, More Signs Inflation is Peaking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/05/oil-tumbles-more-than-8percent-breaks-below-100-as-recession-fears-mount.html"&gt;Oil tumbles as much as 10%, breaks below $100 as recession fears mount&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://electrek.co/2022/07/06/tesla-worlds-largest-electric-car-producer/"&gt;Tesla is still the world’s largest electric car producer despite what you are hearing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tesmanian.com/blogs/tesmanian-blog/analysts-confident-in-teslas-strong-growth-outlook-despite-q2-2022-slowdown"&gt;Analysts Confident in Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Strong Growth Outlook Despite Q2 Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 07-08-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-07082022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-07082022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;31,338.15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-46.40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,899.38&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-3.24&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.08&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,635.31&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;13.96&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,769.36&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.24&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.01&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;24.64&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-1.44&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-5.52&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Volatile day with essentially flat market. All indices had an awesome week. Better than expected job data eased investors mind of recession. I still think we are either already in one or moderate recession is unavoidable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The big news in the market of Elon&amp;rsquo;s backing off from buying Twitter. Tesla stock has seen massive gains in the last few days. I am personally very happy with this news. Purchasing Tweeter at 44 Billion would have been a bad decision in many way. Other highlights of this news are -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Billionaire Elon Musk wants to end his $44 billion deal to buy Twitter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Musk’s lawyer claimed Twitter failed to comply with its obligations in the merger agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter’s board chair Bret Taylor said the company is still committed to closing the deal at the agreed-upon price and plans to pursue legal action to enforce the agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chinese stimulus is in focus. I think China based stocks will be something that will shine in the short term. BABA, NIO and even Tesla will benefit from it. In addition, India and China are buying Russian oil and energy at 30 percent or more discount. This purchase makes manufacturing from these countries very cheap and their massive GDP growth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this is the next bull run, history dictates on average S&amp;amp;P growth about 13 percent after inflation flattens out. We are certainly hoping that is the case here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for signs of market bottoming, which may have already happened.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch for inflation flatten up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/08/elon-musk-notifies-twitter-he-is-terminating-deal.html"&gt;Elon Musk notifies Twitter he is terminating deal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/09/investors-search-for-signs-that-this-rally-might-find-some-traction.html"&gt;Stocks’ latest bounce spurs investors to look for signs that this rally is different from past attempts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/05/oil-tumbles-more-than-8percent-breaks-below-100-as-recession-fears-mount.html"&gt;Oil tumbles as much as 10%, breaks below $100 as recession fears mount&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://electrek.co/2022/07/06/tesla-worlds-largest-electric-car-producer/"&gt;Tesla is still the world’s largest electric car producer despite what you are hearing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tesmanian.com/blogs/tesmanian-blog/analysts-confident-in-teslas-strong-growth-outlook-despite-q2-2022-slowdown"&gt;Analysts Confident in Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Strong Growth Outlook Despite Q2 Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 07-07-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-07072022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-07072022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;31,384.55&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;346.87&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,902.62&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;57.54&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.50&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,621.35&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;259.49&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.28&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,769.60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;42.06&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.43&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;26.08&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.65&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-2.43&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A massive green day today - finally! All indices are up and &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; dropping. China considers massive 250 billion dollar stimulus with historic bond sales. This news helped various chinese and us stocks that have business in China such as Tesla.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shares of Tesla Inc. TSLA, +5.53% advanced 5.53% to $733.63 today, on what proved to be an all-around positive trading session for the stock market. Tesla Inc. closed $509.86 short of its 52-week high ($1,243.49), which the company achieved on November 4th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NIO stock soared today with more than 8 percent gain. NIO is trading 72 percent higher from its recent low on May 12. That is a significant upward price movement. I am hopeful NIO will end up 30 dollars or more by end of 2022.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am still not convinced this upward trajectory is here to stay. I think we will experience more downward pressure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be prepared for recession that is now in my opinion inevitable - agreed by most analyst.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timing the market is nearly impossible!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/07/jobless-claims-edge-up-to-highest-since-january-trade-deficit-hits-2022-low.html"&gt;Jobless claims edge up to highest since January; planned layoffs soar; trade deficit hits 2022 low&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-07-07/china-mulls-220-billion-stimulus-with-unprecedented-bond-sales"&gt;China Considers $220 Billion Stimulus With Unprecedented Bond Sales&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/05/oil-tumbles-more-than-8percent-breaks-below-100-as-recession-fears-mount.html"&gt;Oil tumbles as much as 10%, breaks below $100 as recession fears mount&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://electrek.co/2022/07/06/tesla-worlds-largest-electric-car-producer/"&gt;Tesla is still the world’s largest electric car producer despite what you are hearing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tesmanian.com/blogs/tesmanian-blog/analysts-confident-in-teslas-strong-growth-outlook-despite-q2-2022-slowdown"&gt;Analysts Confident in Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Strong Growth Outlook Despite Q2 Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 07-06-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-07062022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-07062022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;31,037.68&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;69.86&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.23&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,845.08&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;13.69&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.36&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,361.85&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;39.61&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.35&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,727.55&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-13.78&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.79&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;26.73&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.81&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-2.94&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this is the trend, deep red in the morning, ends green at the end. I am not complaining, but just stating that volatility is at its worst or so it seems. All major indexes end up in green territory. Russell 2000 was down which measures growth sectors. VIX dropped another 3 percent and that is great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fed is focused on reducing inflation and they signal they may go with even more strict monetary policy changes. Tesla Stocks again took a negative turn in the morning, ended up green at the end. We are desperately waiting to see some price actions to the upward for Tesla. Stock split decision is coming soon, however, the stock prices do not reflect it (not as of yet anyway). Finally, JPMorgan trims price target for Tesla, says shares could fall more than 40% on weaker deliveries. I absolutely do not agree with this comment but it is what it is!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for BYD, it reported having delivered 638,157 “electric vehicles” during the first half of the year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s what is prompting all those headlines, but what most of the media is failing to highlight is that almost half of BYD’s EV sales are vehicles equipped with internal combustion engines burning gasoline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;314,638 vehicles out of BYD’s reported 638,157 “EV sales” in 2022 are plug-in hybrids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When comparing all-electric vehicles for all-electric vehicles, Tesla still outsold BYD by a significant percentage in 2022 despite its bad quarter. &lt;a href="https://electrek.co/2022/07/06/tesla-worlds-largest-electric-car-producer/"&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be prepared for recession that is now in my opinion inevitable - agreed by most analyst.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timing the market is nearly impossible!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/06/fed-minutes-june-2022.html"&gt;Fed sees ‘more restrictive’ policy as likely if inflation fails to come down, minutes say&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.seeitmarket.com/july-stock-market-seasonality-historical-data-insights-18161/"&gt;Month of July in the stock market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/05/oil-tumbles-more-than-8percent-breaks-below-100-as-recession-fears-mount.html"&gt;Oil tumbles as much as 10%, breaks below $100 as recession fears mount&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://pandaily.com/byd-surpasses-tesla-to-rank-top-in-global-nev-sales-in-h1/"&gt;BYD surpasses Tesla&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tesmanian.com/blogs/tesmanian-blog/analysts-confident-in-teslas-strong-growth-outlook-despite-q2-2022-slowdown"&gt;Analysts Confident in Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Strong Growth Outlook Despite Q2 Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 07-05-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-07052022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-07052022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30,967.82&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-129.44&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,831.39&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;6.06&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,322.24&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;194.40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.75&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,741.33&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;13.57&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.79&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;27.54&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.01&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.04&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The roller coaster ride of the market is worst than the rides in Magic Mountain! Dow Jones had almost 700 point drop but recovered most of it and closed down 0.42%. S&amp;amp;P had a similar effect, it closed positive. Nasdaq had a solid day with almost 2 percent gain. &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; stayed stable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TSLA had a wild ride. At one point lost 60 points, closed in green territory. Volume was high. Deutsche bank says Tesla should have a strong second half. As a Tesla stock holder I think that would be a sign of relief as Tesla stock took a beating in the first half. BYD surpasses EV sales in H1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think the month of July will be very volatile. July is up 48% historically. This &lt;a href="https://www.seeitmarket.com/july-stock-market-seasonality-historical-data-insights-18161/"&gt;link&lt;/a&gt; shows historical data for the month of July. Recession fear pushes oil prices below 100. Most analyst now agree there is a mild/severe recession, except for our president. Note, a recession means, the prices for oil will take a nose down dip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be prepared for recession that is now in my opinion inevitable - agreed by most analyst.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timing the market is nearly impossible!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2022/07/05/tesla-should-have-a-strong-second-half-of-2022-says-deutsche-banks-emmanuel-rosner.html"&gt;Tesla should have a strong second half of 2022, says Deutsche Bank’s Emmanuel Rosner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.seeitmarket.com/july-stock-market-seasonality-historical-data-insights-18161/"&gt;Month of July in the stock market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/05/oil-tumbles-more-than-8percent-breaks-below-100-as-recession-fears-mount.html"&gt;Oil tumbles as much as 10%, breaks below $100 as recession fears mount&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://pandaily.com/byd-surpasses-tesla-to-rank-top-in-global-nev-sales-in-h1/"&gt;BYD surpasses Tesla&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tesmanian.com/blogs/tesmanian-blog/analysts-confident-in-teslas-strong-growth-outlook-despite-q2-2022-slowdown"&gt;Analysts Confident in Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Strong Growth Outlook Despite Q2 Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Trading Posts : Glossary</title><link>/post/glossary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/glossary/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This post will serve as the references for terms that I use in my &lt;a href="/tags/trading"&gt;trading&lt;/a&gt; posts.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 07-01-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-07012022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-07012022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;31,097.26&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-253.88&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.05&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,825.33&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-33.45&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.06&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,127.85&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-149.16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.90&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,727.76&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;19.77&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;26.70&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-2.01&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;7.00&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a saying - all well those ends well. We see that in the market today. In a highly volatile market, with swings of almost 600 points in Dow. At the end all indices end up higher almost one percent. &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; dropped below 28 with 7 percent decline, which indicates general &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;FUD&lt;/a&gt; in market is stabilizing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Federal Reserve tracker of economic growth is pointing to an increased chance that the U.S. economy has entered a recession. As assumed by most, the recession could be here, sooner than most assumed when it would arrive. Nerve wrecking to say the least. We have had such a bad six months, to start the next half of the year, we get this discouraging news feels pretty bad I must admit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TSLA stocks continue to show weakness. Second quarter delivery numbers are scheduled to be released on 7/2/2022. Musk has been quite on his market destructive tweets. I am a die hard fan of Tesla, but I wish Elon was not the CEO of that company. He causes so much turbulence on the stock prices with his silly tweets that it is hard to stay invested in Tesla.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update on 7/2/2022&lt;/strong&gt; : Tesla delivery numbers are out for quarter 2. Highlights are below -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A year ago, Elon Musk’s electric car business delivered 201,250 vehicles in the second quarter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla was hamstrung during the period ending June 30, 2022, by parts shortages, supply chain snarls and Covid restrictions that forced China’s Shanghai factory to close or operate only partially for weeks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chart below demonstrates Tesla&amp;rsquo;s delivery numbers compared to other auto manufacturers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="/img/tesla-delivery-q2-2022.jpg" alt="drawing" style="width:500px;"/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be prepared for recession that is now in my opinion inevitable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timing the market is nearly impossible!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/29/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html"&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 posts worst first half since 1970, Nasdaq falls more than 1% to end the quarter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/30/gm-ford-rising-tesla-falling-in-ev-car-wars-in-us-bank-of-america-analyst-says.html"&gt;GM, Ford rising, Tesla falling in EV ‘car wars’ in U.S., Bank of America analyst says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/30/feds-preferred-inflation-measure-rose-4point7percent-in-may-near-40-year-high.html"&gt;Fed’s preferred inflation measure rose 4.7% in May, around multi-decade highs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/30/the-markets-worst-first-half-in-50-years-has-all-come-down-to-one-thing.html"&gt;The market’s worst first half in 50 years has all come down to one thing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/02/tesla-tsla-q2-2022-vehicle-delivery-and-production-numbers.html"&gt;Tesla delivered 254,695 electric vehicles in the second quarter of 2022&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 6-30-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-06302022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-06302022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30,775.43&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-253.88&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.82&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,785.38&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-33.45&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.88&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,028.74&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-149.16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-1.33&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,707.99&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-11.38&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.96&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;28.60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.44&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.86&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stock market closes with yet another red day. The market’s worst first half in 50 years. This is definitely something to be worried about and not just general &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;FUD&lt;/a&gt;. Feds are determined to get inflation numbers down, however, the persistent inflation is here to stay at least for the short term. War in Ukraine is never ending or so it seems. Oil prices inched up again today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;13 states are working on giving stimulus payment. This is so wrong in my opinion in so many ways. Federally the government is trying to get in control of the inflation, however, state government is going to make it very difficult. I truly don&amp;rsquo;t understand what is the point of all this. . Giving stimulus payment is not that black/white as it appears. It may appear the extra money will help the one that needs it, however, effects of inflation is invisible. For example, a household that makes 50,000 is allowed a stimulus payment of $1,000. But if inflation stays at 6 percent, then the house hold looses 3,000 of the actual buying power. Yielding a loss of 2,000 at the end. Fed’s preferred inflation measure rose 4.7% in May, around multi-decade highs (link to article below)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TSLA continues its path to downward. GM, Ford rising, Tesla falling in EV ‘car wars’ in U.S., Bank of America analyst says. (link to article below). It has been a nasty year for Tesla for sure. Regardless of massive positive news the company stock price is taking heavy hit. The share holders were just requested their vote on the 1-3 stock split. I can imagine, most stock holders will vote positive on the proposal. The stock is the last resort where Tesla stocks may see some massive upward trend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the time of writing this post all indices futures are in red territory for tomorrow 7/1/2022&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be prepared for recession that is now in my opinion inevitable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timing the market is nearly impossible!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/29/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html"&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 posts worst first half since 1970, Nasdaq falls more than 1% to end the quarter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/30/gm-ford-rising-tesla-falling-in-ev-car-wars-in-us-bank-of-america-analyst-says.html"&gt;GM, Ford rising, Tesla falling in EV ‘car wars’ in U.S., Bank of America analyst says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/30/feds-preferred-inflation-measure-rose-4point7percent-in-may-near-40-year-high.html"&gt;Fed’s preferred inflation measure rose 4.7% in May, around multi-decade highs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/30/the-markets-worst-first-half-in-50-years-has-all-come-down-to-one-thing.html"&gt;The market’s worst first half in 50 years has all come down to one thing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 6-29-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-06292022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-06292022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;31,029.31&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;82.32&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.27&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,818.83&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-2.72&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.07&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,177.89&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-3.65&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.03&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,719.37&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-24.79&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-1.86&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;28.16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.71&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A volatile day. Market is giving up slowly all the gains from last week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla stock is under fire, and heading towards hitting 650 a share. Recent news include, lay off of employees. Goldman expects weak Tesla results. Various analysts are revising their second quarter delivery numbers sighting issues with Covid shutdown in China etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;California announced yet another stimulus check for its residents. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it. All for helping the one in need, but a household making $150,000 a year - is not someone who needs help. Also, this stimulus will even put gasoline into fire of inflation. Unbelievable!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nio is also in the downturn. Gave up almost 3 dollars/share in the last few days. Most likely reason is profit taking by the folks who bought it at or around 12/share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crypto remains under severe fire. ETH(Ethereum) are at the time of writing this post down 39.06% over the last 30 days. While, BTC (Bitcoin) has been down 31.91%. That is a massive downturn in a very short period of time. The silver lining on all this, the massive downturn will assure a big run up soon hopefully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fed (Powell) speaks today - hence the market is super nervous. At the time of writing this post, all indexes futures are higher which is definitely a welcome news!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Day trading in the short term, due to massive market volatility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timing the market is nearly impossible!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DCA - Dollar Cost Average focusing on long term gains.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/29/powell-vows-to-prevent-inflation-from-taking-long-run-hold-in-the-us.html"&gt;Powell vows to prevent inflation from taking long-run hold in the U.S.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/28/inflation-relief-checks-worth-up-to-1050-dollars-per-person-may-come-to-california.html"&gt;Millions of Californians may get new stimulus checks worth up to $1,050—here’s who qualifies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/29/crypto-hedge-fund-three-arrows-capital-plunges-into-liquidation.html"&gt;Crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital plunges into liquidation as market crash takes toll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hugo Stock Summary ShortCode Module</title><link>/post/hugo-stock-summary-shortcode/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/hugo-stock-summary-shortcode/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;If you are a regular visitor of my site, you may have noticed, I have started posting daily closing bell stock market &lt;a href="../closing-bell-06282022"&gt;summary&lt;/a&gt;. These pages proceeds with a Market index summary from that day. Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss how I put it together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is a Hugo ShortCode?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shortcodes are simple snippets inside your content files calling built-in or custom templates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parts of the Stock Summary ShortCode&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A JSON Payload for each day to summarize the data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ShortCode HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insertion of the ShortCode into any Mark Down file.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a sample JSON Payload that the Short Code uses -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;code&gt;{
&amp;#34;Index1&amp;#34;: {
&amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Dow&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;30946.99&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;change&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;-491.27&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;percentage&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;-1.56&amp;#34;
},
&amp;#34;Index2&amp;#34;: {
&amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;S&amp;amp;P 500&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;3821.55&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;change&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;-78.56&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;percentage&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;-2.01&amp;#34;
},
&amp;#34;Index3&amp;#34;: {
&amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Nasdaq&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;11181.54&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;change&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;-343.01&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;percentage&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;-2.98&amp;#34;
},
&amp;#34;Index4&amp;#34;: {
&amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Russel 2K&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;1738.84&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;change&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;-32.90&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;percentage&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;-1.86&amp;#34;
},
&amp;#34;Index5&amp;#34;: {
&amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;VIX&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;28.36&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;change&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;1.41&amp;#34;,
&amp;#34;percentage&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;5.23&amp;#34;
}
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Copy the above payload and call it stocks06282022.json. Place this file under your &lt;strong&gt;Data&lt;/strong&gt; folder in Hugo project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create a file called stocks.html and place the following html in it. Save the file under your
&lt;strong&gt;layout\shortcodes&lt;/strong&gt; folder&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Market Summary&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;table class=&amp;#34;table table-dark&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;thead&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th scope=&amp;#34;col&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Index&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th scope=&amp;#34;col&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Value&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th scope=&amp;#34;col&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Change&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th scope=&amp;#34;col&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Percentage&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/thead&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tbody&amp;gt;
{{ $filename := .Get &amp;#34;file&amp;#34; }}
{{ range index .Site.Data $filename }}
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td&amp;gt;{{.name}}&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td&amp;gt;{{lang.FormatNumberCustom 2 .value}}&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td&amp;gt;{{lang.FormatNumberCustom 2 .change}}&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td&amp;gt;{{lang.FormatNumberCustom 2 .percentage}}&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
{{end}}
&amp;lt;/tbody&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/table&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt; I am using bootstrap 4.1 to stylize my table, you can do the same or style it the way you see fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok we are now ready to use the ShortCode! Add the following markup where ever you want to display the stock market summary based on your JSON payload.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;{ { &amp;lt; stocks file=&amp;ldquo;stocks06282022&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt;} }&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt; the parameter the markdown file is passing to the ShortCode module. It is the file name. The trick is every day, you update your JSON file to a new file (call it whatever makes sense to you) save it in the Data folder, and then you get your summary displayed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stock Summary&lt;/strong&gt; JSON payload can be accessed by this service. I am using it in my project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://api.marketstack.com/v1/exchanges?access_key=your-key&amp;amp;limit=3&amp;amp;offset=0"&gt;http://api.marketstack.com/v1/exchanges?access_key=your-key&amp;amp;limit=3&amp;amp;offset=0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope this post was useful!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Repository&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My entire site is available to &lt;a href="https://github.com/yaheya/pulse"&gt;public&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 6-28-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-06282022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-06282022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30,946.99&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-491.27&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-1.56&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,821.55&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-78.56&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-2.01&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,181.54&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-343.01&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-2.98&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,738.84&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-32.90&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-1.86&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;28.36&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.41&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5.23&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Massive red days are back! All indices are in deep red territory with &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; surging back up above 28 again. Cathie Wood believes US is already in a recession. I think as the month June ends and the market wraps up one of the worst six months of the year in stock market history, we can start to see some uptrend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla took a beating today, with the stock price dropping below 700 yet again! Discussing new car quality, JP Morgan states below -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;For Tesla, which ranked 7th from the bottom this year, with the same initial quality score as Mitsubishi, panel alignment and poor paint quality were more common problems than customer issues with the company’s mobile app or infotainment.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt; : Take a deep breath!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/28/ark-invests-cathie-wood-says-the-us-is-already-in-a-recession.html"&gt;ARK Invest’s Cathie Wood says the U.S. is already in a recession&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2022/06/27/crypto-fund-defaults-on-670m-loan-and-bitfury-ceo-says-prices-arent-relevant-cnbc-crypto-world.html"&gt;Crypto fund defaults on $670M loan, and Bitfury CEO says prices aren’t ‘relevant’: CNBC Crypto World&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/28/cathie-wood-explains-bear-market-strategy-slashes-portfolio-by-41percent.html"&gt;Cathie Wood explains her bear market strategy, slashes portfolio to just 34 holdings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/28/new-car-quality-declined-11percent-blame-supply-chain-problems-jd-power.html"&gt;New car quality declined sharply this year with supply chain problems, says J.D. Power&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 6-27-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-06272022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-06272022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;31,438.26&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-62.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,900.11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-11.63&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,524.55&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-83.07&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.72&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,771.74&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;6.01&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.34&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;26.95&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.28&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-1.03&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not a green day but not that red either - which is surprising. A big run on Friday and last week, one would assume a massive pull back today - did not happen. Definitely a good sign. &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/a&gt; ended up green, which is usually indicator for the growth stocks. Read the following this weekend, wanted to share -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As bad as [this year] has been for investors, the good news is previous years that were down at least 15% at the midway point to the year saw the final six months higher every single time, with an average return of nearly 24%,” LPL Financial chief market strategist &lt;a href="https://lplresearch.com/2022/06/22/3-reasons-it-is-so-bad-it-is-good/"&gt;Ryan Detrick&lt;/a&gt; noted earlier this week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I certainly hope Ryan is correct. &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; remaining below 28 is encouraging as well. At the end there are real &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;FUD&lt;/a&gt; exists in market, and I predict if the fear gage does not go down, we will not see sustainable market recovery. The operative term here is &amp;ldquo;sustainable&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt; : Look for short term gains; hold on to the long term securities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/27/robinhood-shares-jump-12percent-and-are-halted-on-report-ftx-may-be-exploring-a-deal.html"&gt;Robinhood shares jump 14% on report FTX may be exploring a deal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2022/06/27/crypto-fund-defaults-on-670m-loan-and-bitfury-ceo-says-prices-arent-relevant-cnbc-crypto-world.html"&gt;Crypto fund defaults on $670M loan, and Bitfury CEO says prices aren’t ‘relevant’: CNBC Crypto World&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 6-24-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-06242022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-06242022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;31,500.68&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;832.32&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.68&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,911.74&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;375.43&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3.34&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,607.62&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;179.11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.62&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,765.74&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;54.07&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3.16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;27.23&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-1.82&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-6.27&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well I am happy to report my prediction for the day of the market was absolutely wrong. All major indices were massively green for the day. Solid gains in S&amp;amp;P, Dow and Nasdaq - what a relief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dow - Up 4.73%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq Up 7.36%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P Up 5.76%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[&lt;a href="glossary"&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/a&gt;](../glossary) Up 4.92%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; Down 16.75%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The above weekly summary is not something to pass by. We definitely see a market rebound. So does this mean the market had bottom, and we can expect a steady gains from here? I am not certain. There are still many market uncertainty out there. Not to mention wide spread &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;FUD&lt;/a&gt;. Although &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; shows promise with less than 27.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prediction for 06/27/2022&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After having a lackluster week, it is possible we will see some pull back the week of 6/27/2022. However, I was recently proven wrong so I am not hundred percent sure that it will be a downturn market. Recently growth stocks are showing signs of recovery and I certainly hope it will continue. Best wishes to everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NIO had a magnificent week with 21.74% up! That is a massive gain. I truly believe this stock is about to hit the sky. I reiterate my price target for NIO 30 by the end of 2022. And 70 plus by 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TSLA stock gained as well. Weekly gain of 14.91%. The gain isn&amp;rsquo;t big as Nio yet but, not bad at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I predict all indexes will end up green in 2022.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tax losses!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus on long term growth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NIO price target by end of 2025 - $70 (minimum)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/23/stock-market-news-futures-open-to-close.html"&gt;Dow rallies 800 points on Friday to cap big comeback week for stocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/24/tech-execs-react-to-roe-v-wade-reversal-gates-sandberg-wojcicki.html"&gt;Tech leaders react to Roe v. Wade reversal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/23/musk-says-tesla-berlin-and-austin-factories-losing-billions-of-dollars.html?&amp;amp;qsearchterm=tesla"&gt;Musk says Tesla’s factories in Berlin and Texas are ‘gigantic money furnaces’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 6-23-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-06232022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-06232022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30,677.36&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;194.23&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.64&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,795.73&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;35.84&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.95&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,232.19&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;179.11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.62&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,711.06&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20.95&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;29.03&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.35&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What a volatile market! I am glad all indices ended up solid green at the closing bell. &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; continues to go down and that is the actual progress. Bond yields slip that is generally good for the market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla stocks are giving up steam, focusing on ongoing supply chain matters, China Covid resurgence. Supply chain issues are not new, however, Musk mentioning it in a crude way just gets the good old &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;FUD&lt;/a&gt; go out of control - hence drop in stock price. Fundamentally, not much has changed. The extreme volatility of Tesla stocks and their stock holders, will get rewarded for sticking through this roller coaster ride - I am sure of it. After closing, TSLA ended up marginally higher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my portfolio, Chinese stocks are doing comparatively better. The main reason is in my opinion, they got beat up bad and the current Chinese government quantitative easing. NIO has been pretty much hosed in the last six months, however, showing signs of relief. Today at one point went above 23 at the time of writing this post was 22.94.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prediction for 06/24/2022&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the time of writing this post, all indexes future are slightly down. I predict tomorrow will be a red day. In addition it is Friday. I am hoping the red day is minimal and not a massive cut to lower level. Fingers crossed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I predict all indexes will end up green in 2022.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tax losses!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus on long term growth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NIO price target by end of 2022 - $30 (minimum)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/22/stock-futures-are-little-changed-after-major-averages-dip-investors-mull-slowdown.html"&gt;Nasdaq rises 1%, Dow adds nearly 200 points in late-day rally&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/22/powell-tells-congress-the-fed-is-strongly-committed-to-bringing-inflation-down.html"&gt;Dow and S&amp;amp;P 500 fall as yields slide, Wall Street weighs recession fears&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/23/musk-says-tesla-berlin-and-austin-factories-losing-billions-of-dollars.html?&amp;amp;qsearchterm=tesla"&gt;Musk says Tesla’s factories in Berlin and Texas are ‘gigantic money furnaces’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Bing Image Gallery and Power Automate</title><link>/post/bing-image-gallery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/bing-image-gallery/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I downloaded the Bing &lt;a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/bing/bing-wallpaper?pc=W016&amp;amp;gclid=CjwKCAjw-8qVBhANEiwAfjXLrs0lbnSDb49ufCoyZPgW1J5XaEwN6n65MOUb7XTVzkHckVbkQWV8AxoC8a4QAvD_BwE"&gt;wallpaper&lt;/a&gt; app. It is actually awesome, everyday I turn on my computer to see what kind of wall paper I get for that day. Most of these are amazing! I use them in my desktop and also as my zoom background! Finally, I created a small &lt;a href="https://powerautomate.microsoft.com/"&gt;Power Automate&lt;/a&gt; routine, that downloads each day Bing wall paper and saves it on to my drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to share some of these &lt;a href="https://www.yaheya.com/gallery"&gt;Bing&lt;/a&gt; images with you! Feel free to download them and use them as you see fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the future, I will post some of the cool things you can do with Power Automate here. Including RPA (Robotic Process Automation).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned and enjoy!!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 6-22-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-06222022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-06222022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30,483.13&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-47.12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,759.89&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-4.90&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.13&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,053.08&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-16.22&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,690.28&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-3.75&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.22&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;28.36&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.41&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5.23&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NO SURPRISE! Red day, although mid trading day all indexes were green but gave up all the gains by the closing bell. I am glad at least, the down turn is small essentially flat. &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; decreased, which is good. Ideally, we want to see it below 20. We have a long way to go up there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla gave up all the mid day gain, at the time of writing this post, down marginally 4.89.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;USWS is getting bought by Profrac at about 1.21 / stock or 0.561 exchange. The stock saw a 37% increase!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NVAX showed some strength, still way down from it&amp;rsquo;s recent highs. I think NVAX going back to above 100 is not happening anytime soon despite various good news for the company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start looking at tax losses!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus on long term growth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Powell tells Congress the Fed is ‘strongly committed’ on inflation, notes recession is a &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/22/powell-tells-congress-the-fed-is-strongly-committed-to-bringing-inflation-down.html"&gt;possibility&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/22/biden-calls-on-congress-to-suspend-gas-tax-what-that-means-for-prices.html"&gt;Biden&lt;/a&gt; calls on Congress to suspend the gas tax — Here’s what that means for prices at the pump&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 6-21-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-06212022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-06212022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30,530.25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;641.47&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,764.79&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;89.95&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.45&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11,069.30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;270.95&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.51&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,694.03&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;28.34&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.70&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30.19&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.84&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-2.71&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Very green day and what a relief! All indexes are showing solid gains. The million dollar question is - the gain is here to stay?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; which measures public sentiment; remains high. In my opinion, &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; &amp;gt;= 28 indicates high [FUD](../(../glossary) (Fear Uncertainty Doubt). Recession fear looms. No doubt, small/large recession is forth coming. Today definitely not a good day to buy anything, as we should watch and monitor the market tomorrow. I certainly hope the gain retains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Massive losses on Crypto appears to be on pause and yes that is a relief. I believe ETH at one time went down to 890 which is a massive discount for anyone who has the dry powder (cash)
to get on ETH. I certainly wish I did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, TSLA is showing a strong day. After weeks of massive downtrend, the stock is gaining some long awaited steam. Elon Musk clarifies company&amp;rsquo;s layoff plans. Musk said the company will lay off 3.5% of the workforce, calling the amount “not super material.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Palantir Technologies — Shares surged more than 7% after Bank of America initiated coverage of the defense tech company with a buy rating. The firm said investors are underestimating the demand for artificial intelligence that should boost Palantir’s stock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Predictions&lt;/strong&gt; : I think Wednesday 6/22/2022 will be red. The question is how red!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt; : &lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/based-on-history-the-next-bull-market-is-just-months-away-and-could-take-the-s-p-500-to-6000-says-bofa-11655475414"&gt;BOFA says next bull market is just months away!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt; : (No Change) Look for short term gains; hold on to the long term securities. Same as before, add crypto into the mix for long term holdings.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Movies/Shows I recommend - Netflix</title><link>/post/movies2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/movies2/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This post is for those who love movies and shows like me. I will try to post rare finds that are not always 100% scoring in rotten tomatoes nevertheless in my opinion well worth it to watch. Today&amp;rsquo;s posts can all be viewed in Netflix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;"&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The Lincoln Lawyer&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Starring:&lt;/strong&gt; Neve Campbell, Manuel Garcia-Rulfo
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Idealistic lawyer Mickey Haller runs his practise out of the back of his Lincoln Town Car, taking on cases big and small across Los Angeles.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong&gt; 6/10
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;"&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Unbelievable (Netflix)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Starring:&lt;/strong&gt; Kaitlyn Dever · Marie Adler ; Toni Collette · Detective Grace Rasmussen ; Merritt Wever · Detective Karen Duvall ; Blake Ellis · Chris McCarthy ;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; When a teen reports being raped, then recants her story, two female detectives follow evidence that could reveal the truth; based on a true story.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong&gt; 7/10
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;"&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Anatomy of a scandal&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Starring:&lt;/strong&gt; Sienna Miller · Sophie Whitehouse ; Rupert Friend · James Whitehouse ; Michelle Dockery · Kate Woodcroft ; Sebastian Selwood; Finn Whitehouse ;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Parliamentary minister James Whitehouse is a happily married man with a loving family home, then a scandalous secret comes to light.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong&gt; 8/10
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;"&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The Mauritanian&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Starring:&lt;/strong&gt; Jodie Foster; Tahar Rahim; Shailene Woodley; Benedict Cumberbatch
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt;A defense attorney, her associate, and a military prosecutor uncover a far-reaching conspiracy while investigating the case of a suspected 9/11 terrorist imprisoned at Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, for six years.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong&gt; 8/10
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Movies/Shows I recommend - Hulu</title><link>/post/movies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/movies/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This post is for those who love movies and shows like me. I will try to post rare finds that are not always 100% scoring in rotten tomatoes nevertheless in my opinion well worth it to watch. Today&amp;rsquo;s post can all be viewed at Hulu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;"&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The Old Man (Hulu)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Starring:&lt;/strong&gt; Jeff Bridges, John Lithgow, Amy Brenneman, Alia Shawkat, E.J. Bonilla &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Dan Chase absconded from the CIA decades ago and has been living off the grid since. When an assassin arrives and tries to take Chase out, the old operative learns that to ensure his future he now must reconcile his past.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong&gt; 8/10
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;"&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Under the Banner of Heaven (Hulu)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Starring:&lt;/strong&gt; Andrew Garfield &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Starring Andrew Garfield, FX’s Under the Banner of Heaven, the limited series inspired by the bestseller by Jon Krakauer, follows the murder of Brenda Wright Lafferty and her baby daughter in a suburb in the Salt Lake Valley. As Detective Jeb Pyre investigates events that transpired, he uncovers buried truths about the origins of the LDS religion and the violent consequences of unyielding faith.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong&gt; 7/10
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;"&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Deep Water (Hulu)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Starring:&lt;/strong&gt; Ben Affleck, Ana De Armas, Tracy Letts
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; A psychological thriller that takes us inside the marriage of picture-perfect Vic (Ben Affleck) and Melinda (Ana de Armas) Van Allen to discover the dangerous mind games they play and what happens to the people that get caught up in them.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong&gt; 6/10
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;"&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The Dropout (Hulu)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Starring:&lt;/strong&gt; Elizabeth Meriwether; Katherine Pope; Michael Showalter; Jordana Mollick; Rebecca Jarvis; Taylor Dunn; Victoria Thompson; Liz Heldens; Liz Hannah.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; In a tale of ambition and fame gone terribly wrong, Elizabeth Holmes develops healthcare technology that puts millions of patients at risk and loses everything in the blink of an eye.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="list-group-item"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong&gt; 6/10
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 6-17-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-06172022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-06172022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;29,888.78&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;62.46&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.13&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,674.84&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8.07&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-0.22&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10,789.35&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;152.25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.43&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,665.69&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15.86&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.96&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;27.23&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-1.82&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-6.27&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As predicted market ended up closing green - somewhat!. Nasdaq which had taken the worst beating yesterday went up the highest. However, after a brutal day yesterday, one should expect a very green day - that was not the case. DJI essentially closed flat while S&amp;amp;P marginally up. I follow VLO which had a nice run and dropped a bit in the past few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crypto currency is certainly experiencing crypto winter. ETH, BTC is down 50 percent or above from their all time highs. The Cryptos I follow are the following -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ETH&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ADAUS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am hopeful ETH will have nice bounce back around September of this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Predictions&lt;/strong&gt; : I think Tuesday 6/21/2022 (6/20/2022 market closed) will be a very green day. With Nasdaq up at least 2 percent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;News&lt;/strong&gt; : Possibility of Ukraine joining Nato.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt; : Look for short term gains; hold on to the long term securities. Same as before, add crypto into the mix for long term holdings.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Closing Bell 6-16-2022</title><link>/post/closing-bell-06162022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/closing-bell-06162022/</guid><description>&lt;h3&gt;Market Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table class="table table-dark"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Index&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Change&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Percentage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;29,927.07&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-741.00&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-2.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3,666.77&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-123.22&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-3.25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Nasdaq&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10,646.10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-453.00&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-4.08&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Russel 2K&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1,649.84&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-81.30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-4.70&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;VIX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;32.95&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3.33&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11.24&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An overall extremely down market today. Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s gain was completely wiped and then added to some more losses. DJIA, Nasdaq hit fresh new lows. All investors want to know, is this the bottom or there are still room to go down! &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; is up almost 11.25 %. This indicates there is FUD (Fear Uncertainty Doubt) exists. In my personal opinion, &lt;a href="../glossary"&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; &amp;gt;= 28 indicates extremely high buying opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TSLA (Tesla) is currently in the downtrend. Although yesterday the stock had a decent day. Nasdaq closed down 4.08 % -453.06 while TSLA down 9.95 % which is almost double the loss than Nasdaq. TSLA had a support level at 650. Today the stock price dropped below that. The next support level exist in 600 level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My prediction for the stock tomorrow &lt;strong&gt;6/17/2022&lt;/strong&gt; is that we will see a bounce back to the positive. The bounce maybe significant as, TSLA stock has taken a major beat down in the recent weeks. The stock price is down YTD approximately 48 percent. The one year price range for TSLA is &lt;strong&gt;$593.50 - $1,243.49&lt;/strong&gt;.TSLA has dropped more than 50 percent from its all time high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt; : Look for short term gains; hold on to the long term securities.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Yaheya.Com new site!</title><link>/post/new-site-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/new-site-2022/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;After many years, moved my personal site to Hugo, previously DotNet Core Azure Web App. Details of current site can be found &lt;a href="/about/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/"&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; which is the main platform this site runs under is a brilliant idea. Not all sites, needs to be generated off from a Database or need backend server technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The site features -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disqus comments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contact form using Formspree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overtime I plan to add many features and post about them as I am doing so. One such post is &lt;a href="../hugo-stock-summary-shortcode"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**RUpdate : Updated Hugo to new version&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title/><link>/post/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/archives/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>