<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pulse</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pulse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review of David Gilmour&#39;s new album : Luck and Strange</title>
      <link>/post/review-luckandstrange/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/review-luckandstrange/</guid>
      <description>🎵 David Gilmour’s much-anticipated album Luck and Strange dropped on September 6, marking his first release in nine years since Rattle That Lock. Fans were eagerly waiting, especially after preview tracks like &amp;ldquo;The Piper’s Call,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Between Two Points,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Dark and Velvet Nights&amp;rdquo; hinted at a mix of the familiar Pink Floyd essence and something new.&#xA;Gilmour doesn’t disappoint. Luck and Strange is a beautifully crafted work with his signature sound—soaring guitar solos, bluesy undertones, and moments of poignant calm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some updates of me</title>
      <link>/post/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/updates/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! I know it&amp;rsquo;s been a while since my last update – things have been incredibly busy with both work and my YouTube channel!&#xA;Work Update:&#xA;On the professional side, we’re making solid progress on our massive ERP project: the Oracle Financial Cloud deployment. This project is a beast, with over a hundred swim lanes of technical and functional scopes. It’s definitely a challenge to keep up with everything that needs to be done between now and our launch date in July 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My YouTube Channel iGluon</title>
      <link>/post/igluon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/igluon/</guid>
      <description>Those who know or follow me know I had my own Sole proprietorship in the early 1990s. I am very proud of what I did with my business back then; unfortunately, I had to close that business eventually due to demand from my daytime job. Recently, I started a new YouTube channel based on my old business name, &amp;ldquo;iGluon.&amp;rdquo; I have a lot of ideas to create content that users may find helpful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing 2024: A Year of Reflection and Renewal</title>
      <link>/post/welcome-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/welcome-2024/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone!&#xA;As we step into the fresh canvas of 2024, I find myself in a reflective mood, contemplating the journey we&amp;rsquo;ve all been through and the exciting path that lies ahead. This isn&amp;rsquo;t just another year; it&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity for growth, resilience, and embracing new possibilities.&#xA;In the realm of software development, the pace of innovation continues to astonish us. As the Chief Software Architect at the University of California, Santa Barbara, I&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed firsthand the remarkable strides we&amp;rsquo;ve made in technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exciting Milestone in my Software Engineering Journey!</title>
      <link>/post/pc-to-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/pc-to-mac/</guid>
      <description>Today, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share a monumental shift in my 30-plus years of software engineering career – the decision to make the Mac my primary work station! 🍎&#xA;Looking back, my journey began with Windows, possibly starting with the era of Windows 3.0. It&amp;rsquo;s where I acquired my foundational computing skills and built the pillars of my engineering career, primarily on various Microsoft platforms.&#xA;As technology advanced, so did my tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depeche Mode Suffer Well Vinyl</title>
      <link>/post/depeche-mode-suffer-well/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/depeche-mode-suffer-well/</guid>
      <description>Diving into the final chapter of our Depeche Mode series with &amp;ldquo;Suffer Well.&amp;rdquo; 🎶 Immerse yourself in the magnetic sounds of Dave Gahan that truly captivate in this track. 🌟 Enjoy the ride! 🚀 Also, spiced it up with clips from the unforgettable Memento Mori concert in Las Vegas, December 2023. 🎤🔥</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phil Collins &amp; Philip Bailey Vinyl</title>
      <link>/post/phil-collins-easy-lover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/phil-collins-easy-lover/</guid>
      <description>🎵 Immerse yourself in the timeless melodies of Phil Collins! 📀 Our latest video features his iconic music, creating a nostalgic vinyl experience. 🚫 No copyright infringement is intended; we&amp;rsquo;re sharing the magic of music purely for the love of it. 💙 Support the artist by grabbing the record and let the tunes become a cherished part of your collection! 🎶 #PhilCollins #VinylExperience #MusicLovers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depeche Mode Concert Memento Mori</title>
      <link>/post/depeche-mode-concert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/depeche-mode-concert/</guid>
      <description>Attended Depeche Mode Concert Memento Mori at Las Vegas on 12/1/2023. My Youtube Post shows some of it, hope you enjoy -</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classic Hits in Vinyl Record</title>
      <link>/post/pl-beegees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/pl-beegees/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iGluon Youtube Channel Playlists</title>
      <link>/post/youtubeplaylist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/youtubeplaylist/</guid>
      <description>Following playlists are now available in my Youtube Channel iGluon. Enjoy!&#xA;Classic Hits in Vinyl Record </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the air tonight - Phil Collins</title>
      <link>/post/in-the-air-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/in-the-air-tonight/</guid>
      <description>This post is a duplicate of the previous one due to a software glitch that caused sound issues.&#xA;🎶 Take a trip down memory lane with the timeless classic &amp;ldquo;In the Air Tonight&amp;rdquo; by Phil Collins, played on a vintage vinyl record. Let the warm crackle and rich tones transport you back in time. 🕰️ Sit back, relax, and experience the magic of this iconic track as it spins on the turntable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Holidays and New year 2023</title>
      <link>/post/quran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/quran/</guid>
      <description>The year 2023 is approaching us quickly. At the end of 2022, I would like to share 12 hand-picked ayaat (verses) from the Quran. May 2023 brings you happiness, peace and prosper.&#xA;So remember me I will remember you: Baqarah 152 Indeed, the mercy of Allah is near to the doers of good. Alaraf 56 Every soul will taste death. And We test you with evil and with good as trial; and to Us you will be returned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Various Trading Tools/Techniques</title>
      <link>/post/trade-technique/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/trade-technique/</guid>
      <description>This post is to introduce to you various Trading Tools and Techniques that may be helpful to you. So let&amp;rsquo;s get on with the list.&#xA;VIX </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Handle</title>
      <link>/post/youtube-handles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/youtube-handles/</guid>
      <description>This post will be a short post for those have a YouTube channel. Google recently introduced, Youtube Handles. YouTube handles helps make it easier for members of the community to find and connect with each other. Your handle will be unique to your channel and will be how people mention you in comments, community posts, and more. My YouTube channel handle is iGluonVinyls. Once you have your unique handle name, then you can get a unique URL for your channel as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pink Floyd Concert in Los Angeles - Roger with brothers!</title>
      <link>/post/pinkfloyd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/pinkfloyd/</guid>
      <description>I am a classic Rock fan. I bought a ticket to go with my brothers and daughter to see Roger Waters - This is not a drill in Cryptoarena Los Angeles.&#xA;The quality of the concert, sound, the environment was absolutely unreal to say the least. However, I must admit Roger&amp;rsquo;s politics is truly crazy. A picture collage of the event with family is below.&#xA;I post a video of the opening in YouTube which got an expected number of views in a short time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 08-22-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-08222022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-08222022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage A disastrous day and has been for almost a week now for all indices. S&amp;amp;P dropped a solid 2.14 percent. Vis spiked up 15.53 percent.&#xA;Strategy&#xA;Cash out for next moderate/severe inflation (2023 most likely) News&#xA;Dow slumps more than 600 points as summer rally fades China holdings of U.S. debt fall below $1 trillion for the first time since 2010 Netflix investors brace for subscriber losses as company works on long-term fixes New Buy Rating for Tesla (TSLA), the Consumer Goods Giant Analysts Confident in Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Strong Growth Outlook Despite Q2 Slowdown </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 08-17-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-08172022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-08172022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 33,980.32 -180.25 -0.69 S&amp;amp;P 500 4,274.04 -32.31 -0.84 Nasdaq 12,938.12 -92.37 -0.81 Russel 2K 1,987.31 -5.96 -0.34 VIX 19.90 1.07 4.42 After almost a month break, I am back writing my closing bells post. Work and personal commitments kept me writing these posts regularly.&#xA;A lot has changed in the market in the last four weeks. It is with great pleasure we see some upside to the market, although today seem to be a wide spread down day on all three major indices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My reflections on Suratul Taha</title>
      <link>/post/taha/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/taha/</guid>
      <description>This post is different than what I have usually post.&#xA;The sura is Taha in Quran, and the sura summarizes the entire adventure when Allah appeared to Prophet Musa in the holy mountains of Tuwa.&#xA;In a few consecutive Ayaat, the sura describes the conversation between Allah and Musa. One of these conversations that touches me the most is when Allah asked Musa to go to Feraun to spread his word.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 07-18-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-07182022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-07182022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 31,072.61 -215.65 -0.69 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,830.85 -32.31 -0.84 Nasdaq 11,360.05 -92.37 -0.81 Russel 2K 1,738.42 -5.96 -0.34 VIX 25.30 1.07 4.42 What a turn of events. Dow up 350 plus in the early trading, only to close -216 at the closing. All major indices gave up their gains and went into solid red. VIX edged up almost 5 percent. At the time of writing this post, all indices futures are flat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 07-15-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-07152022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-07152022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 31,288.26 -192.51 -0.62 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,863.16 72.78 1.92 Nasdaq 11,452.42 201.24 1.79 Russel 2K 1,744.37 36.87 2.16 VIX 24.23 -2.17 -8.22 I have taken few days break from writing my closing bell summary. Many things have happened in the last few days, unfortunately market taking a turn for the worst. All indices were mostly negative.&#xA;Today, there is much needed market rally with all indices in solid green territory and also VIX dropping below 25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 07-12-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-07122022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-07122022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 30,981.33 -192.51 -0.62 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,818.80 -35.63 -0.92 Nasdaq 11,364.73 -107.87 -0.95 Russel 2K 1,728.18 -3.83 -0.22 VIX 27.29 1.12 4.28 Yet another red day - VERY red day I should add. All eyes are on tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s CPI report. I think market is pricing in a very bad news. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe Powell fooled us stating &amp;ldquo;Inflation is transitory&amp;rdquo;. What happened to the &amp;ldquo;transition&amp;rdquo;?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 07-11-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-07112022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-07112022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 31,173.84 -164.31 -0.52 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,854.43 -44.95 -1.15 Nasdaq 11,372.60 -262.71 -2.26 Russel 2K 1,732.01 -37.36 -2.11 VIX 26.17 1.53 6.21 Massive red day - S&amp;amp;P given up almost all the gains from the week prior. It appears, the market takes one step forward two step backward; I don&amp;rsquo;t see how it may change any time soon. Vix went up more than 6 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 07-08-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-07082022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-07082022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 31,338.15 -46.40 -0.15 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,899.38 -3.24 -0.08 Nasdaq 11,635.31 13.96 0.12 Russel 2K 1,769.36 -0.24 -0.01 VIX 24.64 -1.44 -5.52 Volatile day with essentially flat market. All indices had an awesome week. Better than expected job data eased investors mind of recession. I still think we are either already in one or moderate recession is unavoidable.&#xA;The big news in the market of Elon&amp;rsquo;s backing off from buying Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 07-07-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-07072022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-07072022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 31,384.55 346.87 1.12 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,902.62 57.54 1.50 Nasdaq 11,621.35 259.49 2.28 Russel 2K 1,769.60 42.06 2.43 VIX 26.08 -0.65 -2.43 A massive green day today - finally! All indices are up and VIX dropping. China considers massive 250 billion dollar stimulus with historic bond sales. This news helped various chinese and us stocks that have business in China such as Tesla.&#xA;Shares of Tesla Inc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 07-06-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-07062022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-07062022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 31,037.68 69.86 0.23 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,845.08 13.69 0.36 Nasdaq 11,361.85 39.61 0.35 Russel 2K 1,727.55 -13.78 -0.79 VIX 26.73 -0.81 -2.94 So this is the trend, deep red in the morning, ends green at the end. I am not complaining, but just stating that volatility is at its worst or so it seems. All major indexes end up in green territory. Russell 2000 was down which measures growth sectors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 07-05-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-07052022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-07052022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 30,967.82 -129.44 -0.42 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,831.39 6.06 0.16 Nasdaq 11,322.24 194.40 1.75 Russel 2K 1,741.33 13.57 0.79 VIX 27.54 0.01 0.04 The roller coaster ride of the market is worst than the rides in Magic Mountain! Dow Jones had almost 700 point drop but recovered most of it and closed down 0.42%. S&amp;amp;P had a similar effect, it closed positive. Nasdaq had a solid day with almost 2 percent gain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trading Posts : Glossary</title>
      <link>/post/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/glossary/</guid>
      <description>This post will serve as the references for terms that I use in my trading posts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 07-01-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-07012022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-07012022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 31,097.26 -253.88 1.05 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,825.33 -33.45 1.06 Nasdaq 11,127.85 -149.16 0.90 Russel 2K 1,727.76 19.77 1.16 VIX 26.70 -2.01 7.00 There is a saying - all well those ends well. We see that in the market today. In a highly volatile market, with swings of almost 600 points in Dow. At the end all indices end up higher almost one percent. VIX dropped below 28 with 7 percent decline, which indicates general FUD in market is stabilizing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 6-30-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-06302022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-06302022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 30,775.43 -253.88 -0.82 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,785.38 -33.45 -0.88 Nasdaq 11,028.74 -149.16 -1.33 Russel 2K 1,707.99 -11.38 -0.96 VIX 28.60 0.44 1.86 Stock market closes with yet another red day. The market’s worst first half in 50 years. This is definitely something to be worried about and not just general FUD. Feds are determined to get inflation numbers down, however, the persistent inflation is here to stay at least for the short term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 6-29-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-06292022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-06292022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 31,029.31 82.32 0.27 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,818.83 -2.72 -0.07 Nasdaq 11,177.89 -3.65 -0.03 Russel 2K 1,719.37 -24.79 -1.86 VIX 28.16 0.20 -0.71 A volatile day. Market is giving up slowly all the gains from last week.&#xA;Tesla stock is under fire, and heading towards hitting 650 a share. Recent news include, lay off of employees. Goldman expects weak Tesla results. Various analysts are revising their second quarter delivery numbers sighting issues with Covid shutdown in China etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Stock Summary ShortCode Module</title>
      <link>/post/hugo-stock-summary-shortcode/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/hugo-stock-summary-shortcode/</guid>
      <description>If you are a regular visitor of my site, you may have noticed, I have started posting daily closing bell stock market summary. These pages proceeds with a Market index summary from that day. Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss how I put it together.&#xA;What is a Hugo ShortCode?&#xA;Shortcodes are simple snippets inside your content files calling built-in or custom templates.&#xA;Parts of the Stock Summary ShortCode&#xA;A JSON Payload for each day to summarize the data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 6-28-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-06282022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-06282022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 30,946.99 -491.27 -1.56 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,821.55 -78.56 -2.01 Nasdaq 11,181.54 -343.01 -2.98 Russel 2K 1,738.84 -32.90 -1.86 VIX 28.36 1.41 5.23 Massive red days are back! All indices are in deep red territory with VIX surging back up above 28 again. Cathie Wood believes US is already in a recession. I think as the month June ends and the market wraps up one of the worst six months of the year in stock market history, we can start to see some uptrend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 6-27-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-06272022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-06272022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 31,438.26 -62.42 -0.20 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,900.11 -11.63 -0.30 Nasdaq 11,524.55 -83.07 -0.72 Russel 2K 1,771.74 6.01 0.34 VIX 26.95 -0.28 -1.03 Not a green day but not that red either - which is surprising. A big run on Friday and last week, one would assume a massive pull back today - did not happen. Definitely a good sign. Russel 2K ended up green, which is usually indicator for the growth stocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 6-24-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-06242022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-06242022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 31,500.68 832.32 2.68 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,911.74 375.43 3.34 Nasdaq 11,607.62 179.11 1.62 Russel 2K 1,765.74 54.07 3.16 VIX 27.23 -1.82 -6.27 Well I am happy to report my prediction for the day of the market was absolutely wrong. All major indices were massively green for the day. Solid gains in S&amp;amp;P, Dow and Nasdaq - what a relief.&#xA;Weekly Summary&#xA;Dow - Up 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 6-23-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-06232022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-06232022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 30,677.36 194.23 0.64 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,795.73 35.84 0.95 Nasdaq 11,232.19 179.11 1.62 Russel 2K 1,711.06 20.95 1.25 VIX 29.03 0.10 0.35 What a volatile market! I am glad all indices ended up solid green at the closing bell. VIX continues to go down and that is the actual progress. Bond yields slip that is generally good for the market.&#xA;Tesla stocks are giving up steam, focusing on ongoing supply chain matters, China Covid resurgence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bing Image Gallery and Power Automate</title>
      <link>/post/bing-image-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/bing-image-gallery/</guid>
      <description>I downloaded the Bing wallpaper app. It is actually awesome, everyday I turn on my computer to see what kind of wall paper I get for that day. Most of these are amazing! I use them in my desktop and also as my zoom background! Finally, I created a small Power Automate routine, that downloads each day Bing wall paper and saves it on to my drive.&#xA;I wanted to share some of these Bing images with you!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 6-22-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-06222022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-06222022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 30,483.13 -47.12 -0.15 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,759.89 -4.90 -0.13 Nasdaq 11,053.08 -16.22 -0.15 Russel 2K 1,690.28 -3.75 -0.22 VIX 28.36 1.41 5.23 NO SURPRISE! Red day, although mid trading day all indexes were green but gave up all the gains by the closing bell. I am glad at least, the down turn is small essentially flat. VIX decreased, which is good. Ideally, we want to see it below 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 6-21-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-06212022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-06212022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 30,530.25 641.47 2.15 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,764.79 89.95 2.45 Nasdaq 11,069.30 270.95 2.51 Russel 2K 1,694.03 28.34 1.70 VIX 30.19 -0.84 -2.71 A Very green day and what a relief! All indexes are showing solid gains. The million dollar question is - the gain is here to stay?&#xA;VIX which measures public sentiment; remains high. In my opinion, VIX &amp;gt;= 28 indicates high [FUD](../(../glossary) (Fear Uncertainty Doubt).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movies/Shows I recommend - Netflix</title>
      <link>/post/movies2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/movies2/</guid>
      <description>This post is for those who love movies and shows like me. I will try to post rare finds that are not always 100% scoring in rotten tomatoes nevertheless in my opinion well worth it to watch. Today&amp;rsquo;s posts can all be viewed in Netflix.&#xA;The Lincoln Lawyer Starring: Neve Campbell, Manuel Garcia-Rulfo Summary: Idealistic lawyer Mickey Haller runs his practise out of the back of his Lincoln Town Car, taking on cases big and small across Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movies/Shows I recommend - Hulu</title>
      <link>/post/movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/movies/</guid>
      <description>This post is for those who love movies and shows like me. I will try to post rare finds that are not always 100% scoring in rotten tomatoes nevertheless in my opinion well worth it to watch. Today&amp;rsquo;s post can all be viewed at Hulu.&#xA;The Old Man (Hulu) Starring: Jeff Bridges, John Lithgow, Amy Brenneman, Alia Shawkat, E.J. Bonilla Summary: Dan Chase absconded from the CIA decades ago and has been living off the grid since.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 6-17-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-06172022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-06172022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 29,888.78 62.46 -0.13 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,674.84 8.07 -0.22 Nasdaq 10,789.35 152.25 1.43 Russel 2K 1,665.69 15.86 0.96 VIX 27.23 -1.82 -6.27 As predicted market ended up closing green - somewhat!. Nasdaq which had taken the worst beating yesterday went up the highest. However, after a brutal day yesterday, one should expect a very green day - that was not the case. DJI essentially closed flat while S&amp;amp;P marginally up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Bell 6-16-2022</title>
      <link>/post/closing-bell-06162022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/closing-bell-06162022/</guid>
      <description>Market Summary Index Value Change Percentage Dow 29,927.07 -741.00 -2.42 S&amp;amp;P 500 3,666.77 -123.22 -3.25 Nasdaq 10,646.10 -453.00 -4.08 Russel 2K 1,649.84 -81.30 -4.70 VIX 32.95 3.33 11.24 An overall extremely down market today. Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s gain was completely wiped and then added to some more losses. DJIA, Nasdaq hit fresh new lows. All investors want to know, is this the bottom or there are still room to go down! VIX is up almost 11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yaheya.Com new site!</title>
      <link>/post/new-site-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/new-site-2022/</guid>
      <description>After many years, moved my personal site to Hugo, previously DotNet Core Azure Web App. Details of current site can be found here&#xA;Hugo which is the main platform this site runs under is a brilliant idea. Not all sites, needs to be generated off from a Database or need backend server technology.&#xA;The site features -&#xA;Google Analytics Disqus comments Contact form using Formspree Overtime I plan to add many features and post about them as I am doing so.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
