<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Technology on Pulse</title><link>/tags/technology/</link><description>Recent content in Technology on Pulse</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building Scalable and Resilient Cloud Applications</title><link>/post/cloud-native/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/cloud-native/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I recently had the privilege of presenting to the Developer Collaboration group at UC Santa Barbara, a gathering of both Software Developers and Infrastructure Engineers. The topic was &lt;strong&gt;Cloud Native Application Development&lt;/strong&gt;, but the underlying theme was much deeper: the urgent need to bridge the historical divide between those who write the code and those who manage the systems that run it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For years, the industry relied on a Lift and Shift strategy. While this moved us to the cloud, it often failed to unlock true application scalability and infrastructure efficiency. To move forward, we have to acknowledge that infrastructure considerations can no longer be an afterthought—they must become integral to the application development lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Firecrawl LLM Ready AWS Bedrock RAG</title><link>/post/fire-crawl/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/fire-crawl/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey AI builders! Tired of dealing with messy HTML when trying to ground your AWS Bedrock applications with real-world data?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet Firecrawl (&lt;a href="https://www.firecrawl.dev"&gt;https://www.firecrawl.dev&lt;/a&gt;), the AI-first web crawling and scraping API that&amp;rsquo;s changing the RAG game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is Firecrawl?
Firecrawl is designed to solve the headache of getting clean web data for Large Language Models (LLMs). Instead of wrestling with traditional scrapers, Firecrawl:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crawls entire websites or scrapes single pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cleans the content automatically (removes headers, footers, ads).&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Bedrock's Game Changer: Why Cross-Region LLM Inference is a Must-Have</title><link>/post/bedrock/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/bedrock/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;As Chief Software Architect at UC Santa Barbara, I focus on integrating cutting-edge cloud features like AWS Bedrock. For enterprise LLM deployment, we must solve three non-negotiables: latency, data gravity, and resiliency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cross-region inference in Bedrock is the definitive answer, moving LLM strategy from experiment to production-grade architecture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Pillars of Multi-Region LLM Architecture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;High Resiliency and Failover
Single-region deployment is a critical vulnerability. Cross-region inference allows immediate, automatic failover (e.g., from us-east-1 to us-west-2). This maintains API parity and model consistency across geographies, guaranteeing uninterrupted service for critical applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>YouTube Handle</title><link>/post/youtube-handles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/youtube-handles/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This post will be a short post for those have a YouTube channel. Google recently introduced, Youtube Handles. YouTube handles helps make it easier for members of the community to find and connect with each other. Your handle will be unique to your channel and will be how people mention you in comments, community posts, and more. My YouTube channel handle is iGluonVinyls. Once you have your unique handle name, then you can get a unique URL for your channel as well. For example mine is &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/igluonvinyls"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/igluonvinyls&lt;/a&gt; This URL is much easier to remember than the previous GUID based URL.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hugo Stock Summary ShortCode Module</title><link>/post/hugo-stock-summary-shortcode/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/hugo-stock-summary-shortcode/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;If you are a regular visitor of my site, you may have noticed, I have started posting daily closing bell stock market &lt;a href="../closing-bell-06282022"&gt;summary&lt;/a&gt;. These pages proceeds with a Market index summary from that day. Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss how I put it together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is a Hugo ShortCode?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shortcodes are simple snippets inside your content files calling built-in or custom templates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parts of the Stock Summary ShortCode&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A JSON Payload for each day to summarize the data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ShortCode HTML&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insertion of the ShortCode into any Mark Down file.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a sample JSON Payload that the Short Code uses -&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Bing Image Gallery and Power Automate</title><link>/post/bing-image-gallery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/bing-image-gallery/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I downloaded the Bing &lt;a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/bing/bing-wallpaper?pc=W016&amp;amp;gclid=CjwKCAjw-8qVBhANEiwAfjXLrs0lbnSDb49ufCoyZPgW1J5XaEwN6n65MOUb7XTVzkHckVbkQWV8AxoC8a4QAvD_BwE"&gt;wallpaper&lt;/a&gt; app. It is actually awesome, everyday I turn on my computer to see what kind of wall paper I get for that day. Most of these are amazing! I use them in my desktop and also as my zoom background! Finally, I created a small &lt;a href="https://powerautomate.microsoft.com/"&gt;Power Automate&lt;/a&gt; routine, that downloads each day Bing wall paper and saves it on to my drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to share some of these &lt;a href="https://www.yaheya.com/gallery"&gt;Bing&lt;/a&gt; images with you! Feel free to download them and use them as you see fit.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Yaheya.Com new site!</title><link>/post/new-site-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/new-site-2022/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;After many years, moved my personal site to Hugo, previously DotNet Core Azure Web App. Details of current site can be found &lt;a href="/about/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/"&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; which is the main platform this site runs under is a brilliant idea. Not all sites, needs to be generated off from a Database or need backend server technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The site features -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disqus comments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contact form using Formspree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overtime I plan to add many features and post about them as I am doing so. One such post is &lt;a href="../hugo-stock-summary-shortcode"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>