<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hulu on Pulse</title><link>/tags/hulu/</link><description>Recent content in Hulu on Pulse</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/hulu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Movies/Shows I recommend - Hulu</title><link>/post/movies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/movies/</guid><description>&lt;p>This post is for those who love movies and shows like me. I will try to post rare finds that are not always 100% scoring in rotten tomatoes nevertheless in my opinion well worth it to watch. Today&amp;rsquo;s post can all be viewed at Hulu.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;">
 &lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;">
 &lt;strong>The Old Man (Hulu)&lt;/strong> 
 &lt;/li>
 &lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Starring:&lt;/strong> Jeff Bridges, John Lithgow, Amy Brenneman, Alia Shawkat, E.J. Bonilla &lt;br />
&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Summary:&lt;/strong> Dan Chase absconded from the CIA decades ago and has been living off the grid since. When an assassin arrives and tries to take Chase out, the old operative learns that to ensure his future he now must reconcile his past.
&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong> 8/10
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;">
 &lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;">
 &lt;strong>Under the Banner of Heaven (Hulu)&lt;/strong> 
 &lt;/li>
 &lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Starring:&lt;/strong> Andrew Garfield &lt;br />
&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Summary:&lt;/strong> Starring Andrew Garfield, FX’s Under the Banner of Heaven, the limited series inspired by the bestseller by Jon Krakauer, follows the murder of Brenda Wright Lafferty and her baby daughter in a suburb in the Salt Lake Valley. As Detective Jeb Pyre investigates events that transpired, he uncovers buried truths about the origins of the LDS religion and the violent consequences of unyielding faith. 
&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong> 7/10
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;">
 &lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;">
 &lt;strong>Deep Water (Hulu)&lt;/strong> 
 &lt;/li>
 &lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Starring:&lt;/strong> Ben Affleck, Ana De Armas, Tracy Letts 
&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Summary:&lt;/strong> A psychological thriller that takes us inside the marriage of picture-perfect Vic (Ben Affleck) and Melinda (Ana de Armas) Van Allen to discover the dangerous mind games they play and what happens to the people that get caught up in them. 
&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong> 6/10
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;ul class="list-group w-50" style="width:100%;">
 &lt;li class="list-group-item" style="color:blue;">
 &lt;strong>The Dropout (Hulu)&lt;/strong> 
 &lt;/li>
 &lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Starring:&lt;/strong> Elizabeth Meriwether; Katherine Pope; Michael Showalter; Jordana Mollick; Rebecca Jarvis; Taylor Dunn; Victoria Thompson; Liz Heldens; Liz Hannah. 
&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Summary:&lt;/strong> In a tale of ambition and fame gone terribly wrong, Elizabeth Holmes develops healthcare technology that puts millions of patients at risk and loses everything in the blink of an eye.
&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="list-group-item">
&lt;strong>Yaheya's Stars&lt;/strong> 6/10
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>