<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>personal on Pulse</title><link>/tags/personal/</link><description>Recent content in personal on Pulse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Embracing 2024: A Year of Reflection and Renewal</title><link>/post/welcome-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/welcome-2024/</guid><description>Hey everyone!
As we step into the fresh canvas of 2024, I find myself in a reflective mood, contemplating the journey we&amp;rsquo;ve all been through and the exciting path that lies ahead. This isn&amp;rsquo;t just another year; it&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity for growth, resilience, and embracing new possibilities.
In the realm of software development, the pace of innovation continues to astonish us. As the Chief Software Architect at the University of California, Santa Barbara, I&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed firsthand the remarkable strides we&amp;rsquo;ve made in technology.</description></item><item><title>Depeche Mode Suffer Well Vinyl</title><link>/post/depeche-mode-suffer-well/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/depeche-mode-suffer-well/</guid><description>Diving into the final chapter of our Depeche Mode series with &amp;ldquo;Suffer Well.&amp;rdquo; 🎶 Immerse yourself in the magnetic sounds of Dave Gahan that truly captivate in this track. 🌟 Enjoy the ride! 🚀 Also, spiced it up with clips from the unforgettable Memento Mori concert in Las Vegas, December 2023. 🎤🔥</description></item><item><title>Phil Collins &amp; Philip Bailey Vinyl</title><link>/post/phil-collins-easy-lover/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/phil-collins-easy-lover/</guid><description>🎵 Immerse yourself in the timeless melodies of Phil Collins! 📀 Our latest video features his iconic music, creating a nostalgic vinyl experience. 🚫 No copyright infringement is intended; we&amp;rsquo;re sharing the magic of music purely for the love of it. 💙 Support the artist by grabbing the record and let the tunes become a cherished part of your collection! 🎶 #PhilCollins #VinylExperience #MusicLovers</description></item><item><title>Depeche Mode Concert Memento Mori</title><link>/post/depeche-mode-concert/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/depeche-mode-concert/</guid><description>Attended Depeche Mode Concert Memento Mori at Las Vegas on 12/1/2023. My Youtube Post shows some of it, hope you enjoy -</description></item><item><title>Classic Hits in Vinyl Record</title><link>/post/pl-beegees/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/pl-beegees/</guid><description/></item><item><title>iGluon Youtube Channel Playlists</title><link>/post/youtubeplaylist/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/youtubeplaylist/</guid><description>Following playlists are now available in my Youtube Channel iGluon. Enjoy!
Classic Hits in Vinyl Record</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays and New year 2023</title><link>/post/quran/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/quran/</guid><description>The year 2023 is approaching us quickly. At the end of 2022, I would like to share 12 hand-picked ayaat (verses) from the Quran. May 2023 brings you happiness, peace and prosper.
So remember me I will remember you: Baqarah 152 Indeed, the mercy of Allah is near to the doers of good. Alaraf 56 Every soul will taste death. And We test you with evil and with good as trial; and to Us you will be returned.</description></item><item><title>My YouTube Channel iGluon</title><link>/post/igluon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/igluon/</guid><description>Those who know or follow me know I had my own Sole proprietorship in the early 1990s. I am very proud of what I did with my business back then; unfortunately, I had to close that business eventually due to demand from my daytime job. Recently, I started a new YouTube channel based on my old business name, &amp;ldquo;iGluon.&amp;rdquo; I have a lot of ideas to create content that users may find helpful.</description></item><item><title>Pink Floyd Concert in Los Angeles - Roger with brothers!</title><link>/post/pinkfloyd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/pinkfloyd/</guid><description>I am a classic Rock fan. I bought a ticket to go with my brothers and daughter to see Roger Waters - This is not a drill in Cryptoarena Los Angeles.
The quality of the concert, sound, the environment was absolutely unreal to say the least. However, I must admit Roger&amp;rsquo;s politics is truly crazy. A picture collage of the event with family is below.
I post a video of the opening in YouTube which got an expected number of views in a short time.</description></item><item><title>My reflections on Suratul Taha</title><link>/post/taha/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/taha/</guid><description>This post is different than what I have usually post.
The sura is Taha in Quran, and the sura summarizes the entire adventure when Allah appeared to Prophet Musa in the holy mountains of Tuwa.
In a few consecutive Ayaat, the sura describes the conversation between Allah and Musa. One of these conversations that touches me the most is when Allah asked Musa to go to Feraun to spread his word.</description></item><item><title>Bing Image Gallery and Power Automate</title><link>/post/bing-image-gallery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/bing-image-gallery/</guid><description>I downloaded the Bing wallpaper app. It is actually awesome, everyday I turn on my computer to see what kind of wall paper I get for that day. Most of these are amazing! I use them in my desktop and also as my zoom background! Finally, I created a small Power Automate routine, that downloads each day Bing wall paper and saves it on to my drive.
I wanted to share some of these Bing images with you!</description></item><item><title>Movies/Shows I recommend - Netflix</title><link>/post/movies2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/movies2/</guid><description>This post is for those who love movies and shows like me. I will try to post rare finds that are not always 100% scoring in rotten tomatoes nevertheless in my opinion well worth it to watch. Today&amp;rsquo;s posts can all be viewed in Netflix.
The Lincoln Lawyer Starring: Neve Campbell, Manuel Garcia-Rulfo Summary: Idealistic lawyer Mickey Haller runs his practise out of the back of his Lincoln Town Car, taking on cases big and small across Los Angeles.</description></item><item><title>Movies/Shows I recommend - Hulu</title><link>/post/movies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/movies/</guid><description>This post is for those who love movies and shows like me. I will try to post rare finds that are not always 100% scoring in rotten tomatoes nevertheless in my opinion well worth it to watch. Today&amp;rsquo;s post can all be viewed at Hulu.
The Old Man (Hulu) Starring: Jeff Bridges, John Lithgow, Amy Brenneman, Alia Shawkat, E.J. Bonilla Summary: Dan Chase absconded from the CIA decades ago and has been living off the grid since.</description></item><item><title>Yaheya.Com new site!</title><link>/post/new-site-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/new-site-2022/</guid><description>After many years, moved my personal site to Hugo, previously DotNet Core Azure Web App. Details of current site can be found here
Hugo which is the main platform this site runs under is a brilliant idea. Not all sites, needs to be generated off from a Database or need backend server technology.
The site features -
Google Analytics Disqus comments Contact form using Formspree Overtime I plan to add many features and post about them as I am doing so.</description></item></channel></rss>